(window["webpackJsonp"] = window["webpackJsonp"] || []).push([[0],{

/***/ "./src/app/dev-center/dev-center-routing.module.ts":
/*!*********************************************************!*\
  !*** ./src/app/dev-center/dev-center-routing.module.ts ***!
  \*********************************************************/
/*! exports provided: DevCenterRoutingModule */
/***/ (function(module, __webpack_exports__, __webpack_require__) {

"use strict";
__webpack_require__.r(__webpack_exports__);
/* harmony export (binding) */ __webpack_require__.d(__webpack_exports__, "DevCenterRoutingModule", function() { return DevCenterRoutingModule; });
/* harmony import */ var tslib__WEBPACK_IMPORTED_MODULE_0__ = __webpack_require__(/*! tslib */ "./node_modules/tslib/tslib.es6.js");
/* harmony import */ var _angular_core__WEBPACK_IMPORTED_MODULE_1__ = __webpack_require__(/*! @angular/core */ "./node_modules/@angular/core/fesm5/core.js");
/* harmony import */ var _angular_router__WEBPACK_IMPORTED_MODULE_2__ = __webpack_require__(/*! @angular/router */ "./node_modules/@angular/router/fesm5/router.js");
/* harmony import */ var _error_page_error_page_component__WEBPACK_IMPORTED_MODULE_3__ = __webpack_require__(/*! ./error-page/error-page.component */ "./src/app/dev-center/error-page/error-page.component.ts");
/* harmony import */ var _app_auth_guards__WEBPACK_IMPORTED_MODULE_4__ = __webpack_require__(/*! @app/auth/_guards */ "./src/app/auth/_guards/index.ts");





var routes = [
    {
        path: 'warnings',
        component: _error_page_error_page_component__WEBPACK_IMPORTED_MODULE_3__["ErrorPageComponent"],
        canActivate: [_app_auth_guards__WEBPACK_IMPORTED_MODULE_4__["AuthCanActivateGuard"]],
        data: {
            expectedRoles: [1]
        }
    },
    {
        path: '',
        redirectTo: 'warnings',
        pathMatch: 'full'
    }
];
var DevCenterRoutingModule = /** @class */ (function () {
    function DevCenterRoutingModule() {
    }
    DevCenterRoutingModule = tslib__WEBPACK_IMPORTED_MODULE_0__["__decorate"]([
        Object(_angular_core__WEBPACK_IMPORTED_MODULE_1__["NgModule"])({
            imports: [_angular_router__WEBPACK_IMPORTED_MODULE_2__["RouterModule"].forChild(routes)],
            exports: [_angular_router__WEBPACK_IMPORTED_MODULE_2__["RouterModule"]]
        })
    ], DevCenterRoutingModule);
    return DevCenterRoutingModule;
}());



/***/ }),

/***/ "./src/app/dev-center/dev-center.module.ts":
/*!*************************************************!*\
  !*** ./src/app/dev-center/dev-center.module.ts ***!
  \*************************************************/
/*! exports provided: DevCenterModule */
/***/ (function(module, __webpack_exports__, __webpack_require__) {

"use strict";
__webpack_require__.r(__webpack_exports__);
/* harmony export (binding) */ __webpack_require__.d(__webpack_exports__, "DevCenterModule", function() { return DevCenterModule; });
/* harmony import */ var tslib__WEBPACK_IMPORTED_MODULE_0__ = __webpack_require__(/*! tslib */ "./node_modules/tslib/tslib.es6.js");
/* harmony import */ var _angular_core__WEBPACK_IMPORTED_MODULE_1__ = __webpack_require__(/*! @angular/core */ "./node_modules/@angular/core/fesm5/core.js");
/* harmony import */ var _angular_common__WEBPACK_IMPORTED_MODULE_2__ = __webpack_require__(/*! @angular/common */ "./node_modules/@angular/common/fesm5/common.js");
/* harmony import */ var _angular_forms__WEBPACK_IMPORTED_MODULE_3__ = __webpack_require__(/*! @angular/forms */ "./node_modules/@angular/forms/fesm5/forms.js");
/* harmony import */ var _widget_widget_module__WEBPACK_IMPORTED_MODULE_4__ = __webpack_require__(/*! ../widget/widget.module */ "./src/app/widget/widget.module.ts");
/* harmony import */ var _dev_center_routing_module__WEBPACK_IMPORTED_MODULE_5__ = __webpack_require__(/*! ./dev-center-routing.module */ "./src/app/dev-center/dev-center-routing.module.ts");
/* harmony import */ var _error_page_error_page_component__WEBPACK_IMPORTED_MODULE_6__ = __webpack_require__(/*! ./error-page/error-page.component */ "./src/app/dev-center/error-page/error-page.component.ts");







var DevCenterModule = /** @class */ (function () {
    function DevCenterModule() {
    }
    DevCenterModule = tslib__WEBPACK_IMPORTED_MODULE_0__["__decorate"]([
        Object(_angular_core__WEBPACK_IMPORTED_MODULE_1__["NgModule"])({
            declarations: [_error_page_error_page_component__WEBPACK_IMPORTED_MODULE_6__["ErrorPageComponent"]],
            imports: [
                _angular_common__WEBPACK_IMPORTED_MODULE_2__["CommonModule"],
                _widget_widget_module__WEBPACK_IMPORTED_MODULE_4__["WidgetModule"],
                _angular_forms__WEBPACK_IMPORTED_MODULE_3__["ReactiveFormsModule"],
                _angular_forms__WEBPACK_IMPORTED_MODULE_3__["FormsModule"],
                _dev_center_routing_module__WEBPACK_IMPORTED_MODULE_5__["DevCenterRoutingModule"]
            ]
        })
    ], DevCenterModule);
    return DevCenterModule;
}());



/***/ }),

/***/ "./src/app/dev-center/error-page/error-page.component.html":
/*!*****************************************************************!*\
  !*** ./src/app/dev-center/error-page/error-page.component.html ***!
  \*****************************************************************/
/*! no static exports found */
/***/ (function(module, exports) {

module.exports = "<div class=\"detail-container list-container\">\r\n    <div class=\"detail-page-header page-list-title\">\r\n        <span class=\"detail-page-header-label \">Generation Warnings / Errors</span>\r\n    </div>\r\n    <form [formGroup]=\"form\" class=\"float-right col-md-12\">\r\n        <select formControlName=\"warning\" [(ngModel)]=\"warning\" (change)=\"onGenerationChange($event)\" *ngIf=\"warnings && warnings.length\" class=\"float-right\">\r\n        <option *ngFor=\"let warning of warnings\" [ngValue]=\"warning.id\">\r\n          {{ warning.action }} \r\n          <div> ( {{ warning.dateTime | date:'medium' }} )</div>\r\n        </option>\r\n      </select>\r\n    </form>\r\n    <div class=\"detail-page-content float-left col-md-12\">\r\n        <app-vs-grid [gridConfig]=gridConfig></app-vs-grid>\r\n    </div>\r\n</div>"

/***/ }),

/***/ "./src/app/dev-center/error-page/error-page.component.scss":
/*!*****************************************************************!*\
  !*** ./src/app/dev-center/error-page/error-page.component.scss ***!
  \*****************************************************************/
/*! no static exports found */
/***/ (function(module, exports) {

module.exports = ":host ::ng-deep .error-type-warning {\n  background: #FFEB3B;\n  letter-spacing: 1px;\n  color: #673AB7 !important; }\n\n:host ::ng-deep .error-type-error {\n  background-color: #f1584dfa;\n  letter-spacing: 1px; }\n\nselect[formcontrolname=\"warning\"],\nselect[formcontrolname=\"warning\"] option {\n  font-size: 14px;\n  font-family: monospace;\n  padding: 3px 10px 3px 0px;\n  margin: 15px 15px 0px 15px; }\n\n/*# sourceMappingURL=data:application/json;base64,eyJ2ZXJzaW9uIjozLCJzb3VyY2VzIjpbInNyYy9hcHAvZGV2LWNlbnRlci9lcnJvci1wYWdlL0Q6XFxQUk9KRUNUU19GT0xERVJcXEVWQVxcY29yb25hZ29mcm9udGVuZF9sYXRlc3Qvc3JjXFxhcHBcXGRldi1jZW50ZXJcXGVycm9yLXBhZ2VcXGVycm9yLXBhZ2UuY29tcG9uZW50LnNjc3MiXSwibmFtZXMiOltdLCJtYXBwaW5ncyI6IkFBQUE7RUFDSSxtQkFBbUI7RUFDbkIsbUJBQW1CO0VBQ25CLHlCQUF5QixFQUFBOztBQUc3QjtFQUNJLDJCQUEyQjtFQUMzQixtQkFBbUIsRUFBQTs7QUFHdkI7O0VBRUksZUFBZTtFQUNmLHNCQUFzQjtFQUN0Qix5QkFBeUI7RUFDekIsMEJBQTBCLEVBQUEiLCJmaWxlIjoic3JjL2FwcC9kZXYtY2VudGVyL2Vycm9yLXBhZ2UvZXJyb3ItcGFnZS5jb21wb25lbnQuc2NzcyIsInNvdXJjZXNDb250ZW50IjpbIjpob3N0IDo6bmctZGVlcCAuZXJyb3ItdHlwZS13YXJuaW5nIHtcclxuICAgIGJhY2tncm91bmQ6ICNGRkVCM0I7XHJcbiAgICBsZXR0ZXItc3BhY2luZzogMXB4O1xyXG4gICAgY29sb3I6ICM2NzNBQjcgIWltcG9ydGFudDtcclxufVxyXG5cclxuOmhvc3QgOjpuZy1kZWVwIC5lcnJvci10eXBlLWVycm9yIHtcclxuICAgIGJhY2tncm91bmQtY29sb3I6ICNmMTU4NGRmYTtcclxuICAgIGxldHRlci1zcGFjaW5nOiAxcHg7XHJcbn1cclxuXHJcbnNlbGVjdFtmb3JtY29udHJvbG5hbWU9XCJ3YXJuaW5nXCJdLFxyXG5zZWxlY3RbZm9ybWNvbnRyb2xuYW1lPVwid2FybmluZ1wiXSBvcHRpb24ge1xyXG4gICAgZm9udC1zaXplOiAxNHB4O1xyXG4gICAgZm9udC1mYW1pbHk6IG1vbm9zcGFjZTtcclxuICAgIHBhZGRpbmc6IDNweCAxMHB4IDNweCAwcHg7XHJcbiAgICBtYXJnaW46IDE1cHggMTVweCAwcHggMTVweDtcclxufSJdfQ== */"

/***/ }),

/***/ "./src/app/dev-center/error-page/error-page.component.ts":
/*!***************************************************************!*\
  !*** ./src/app/dev-center/error-page/error-page.component.ts ***!
  \***************************************************************/
/*! exports provided: ErrorPageComponent */
/***/ (function(module, __webpack_exports__, __webpack_require__) {

"use strict";
__webpack_require__.r(__webpack_exports__);
/* harmony export (binding) */ __webpack_require__.d(__webpack_exports__, "ErrorPageComponent", function() { return ErrorPageComponent; });
/* harmony import */ var tslib__WEBPACK_IMPORTED_MODULE_0__ = __webpack_require__(/*! tslib */ "./node_modules/tslib/tslib.es6.js");
/* harmony import */ var _angular_core__WEBPACK_IMPORTED_MODULE_1__ = __webpack_require__(/*! @angular/core */ "./node_modules/@angular/core/fesm5/core.js");
/* harmony import */ var _angular_forms__WEBPACK_IMPORTED_MODULE_2__ = __webpack_require__(/*! @angular/forms */ "./node_modules/@angular/forms/fesm5/forms.js");
/* harmony import */ var _assets_devcenter_gen_errors_json__WEBPACK_IMPORTED_MODULE_3__ = __webpack_require__(/*! @assets/devcenter/gen-errors.json */ "./src/assets/devcenter/gen-errors.json");
var _assets_devcenter_gen_errors_json__WEBPACK_IMPORTED_MODULE_3___namespace = /*#__PURE__*/__webpack_require__.t(/*! @assets/devcenter/gen-errors.json */ "./src/assets/devcenter/gen-errors.json", 1);




var ErrorPageComponent = /** @class */ (function () {
    function ErrorPageComponent(formBuilder) {
        this.formBuilder = formBuilder;
        this.warnings = _assets_devcenter_gen_errors_json__WEBPACK_IMPORTED_MODULE_3__;
        this.warning = this.warnings[0] ? this.warnings[0].id : '';
        this.form = new _angular_forms__WEBPACK_IMPORTED_MODULE_2__["FormGroup"]({
            warning: new _angular_forms__WEBPACK_IMPORTED_MODULE_2__["FormControl"](this.warnings[0])
        });
    }
    ErrorPageComponent.prototype.ngOnInit = function () {
        this.loadGridConfig();
    };
    ErrorPageComponent.prototype.loadGridConfig = function () {
        var self = this;
        this.gridConfig = {
            ordering: true,
            customOrdering: false,
            data: (this.warnings && this.warnings[0]) ? this.warnings[0].items : [],
            disableSelection: true,
            columns: [
                {
                    data: 'id',
                    name: 'id',
                    title: 'S.No',
                    orderable: false
                },
                {
                    data: 'sheetLink',
                    name: 'sheetLink',
                    title: 'Sheet Link',
                    orderable: false,
                    render: function (data, type, row, meta) {
                        return '<a href=' + data + ' target="blank"> ' + row.sheetName + ' </a>';
                    }
                },
                {
                    data: 'tab',
                    name: 'tab',
                    title: 'Tab Name',
                    orderable: false
                },
                {
                    data: 'rowIdx',
                    name: 'cell',
                    title: 'Cell',
                    orderable: false,
                    render: function (data, type, row, meta) {
                        var colIdx = row.column;
                        var colStr = self.getColCharIdx(colIdx - 1);
                        return colStr + row.rowIdx;
                    }
                },
                {
                    data: 'type',
                    name: 'type',
                    title: 'Type',
                    orderable: false,
                    conditionalColorField: 'type',
                    conditionalColor: {
                        // tslint:disable-next-line: object-literal-key-quotes
                        'Error': 'error-type-error',
                        'Warning': 'error-type-warning'
                    }
                },
                {
                    data: 'problem',
                    name: 'problem',
                    title: 'description',
                    orderable: false
                },
                {
                    data: 'solution',
                    name: 'solution',
                    title: 'Possible solutions',
                    orderable: false
                }
            ],
            onInitComplete: function (dtInstance, settings, json) {
                self.dtInstance = dtInstance;
            }
        };
    };
    ErrorPageComponent.prototype.onGenerationChange = function (event) {
        var selectedIdx = this.warning;
        this.dtInstance.clear();
        this.dtInstance.rows.add(this.warnings[selectedIdx].items).draw();
    };
    ErrorPageComponent.prototype.getColCharIdx = function (colIdx) {
        var charCode;
        if (colIdx <= 25) {
            charCode = parseInt(colIdx) + parseInt('65');
            return String.fromCharCode(charCode);
        }
        else {
            var firstCharCode = Math.floor(colIdx / 26) - 1;
            var firstChar = this.getColCharIdx(firstCharCode);
            var lastCharCode = colIdx % 26;
            var lastChar = this.getColCharIdx(lastCharCode);
            return firstChar + lastChar;
        }
    };
    ErrorPageComponent = tslib__WEBPACK_IMPORTED_MODULE_0__["__decorate"]([
        Object(_angular_core__WEBPACK_IMPORTED_MODULE_1__["Component"])({
            selector: 'app-error-page',
            template: __webpack_require__(/*! ./error-page.component.html */ "./src/app/dev-center/error-page/error-page.component.html"),
            styles: [__webpack_require__(/*! ./error-page.component.scss */ "./src/app/dev-center/error-page/error-page.component.scss")]
        }),
        tslib__WEBPACK_IMPORTED_MODULE_0__["__metadata"]("design:paramtypes", [_angular_forms__WEBPACK_IMPORTED_MODULE_2__["FormBuilder"]])
    ], ErrorPageComponent);
    return ErrorPageComponent;
}());



/***/ }),

/***/ "./src/assets/devcenter/gen-errors.json":
/*!**********************************************!*\
  !*** ./src/assets/devcenter/gen-errors.json ***!
  \**********************************************/
/*! exports provided: 0, 1, 2, 3, 4, 5, 6, 7, 8, 9, default */
/***/ (function(module) {

module.exports = [{"id":1,"action":"Detail Page Generation","dateTime":1585124055360,"items":[{"id":1,"sheetLink":"13zbPhkw6Wccwa9QPvUYFKEcEvLqHk9c9KY-9EQkMqo0","sheetName":"Eva - Module Template V1.0 - CoronaGo","tab":"Data Model","type":"Warning","problem":"Allowed values are missing for `Hospital Name`","solution":"For Data type Checkbox/CheckboxGroup/DropDown/RadioButton/Multiselect allowed values should be configured","rowIdx":"59","column":"7"},{"id":2,"sheetLink":"13zbPhkw6Wccwa9QPvUYFKEcEvLqHk9c9KY-9EQkMqo0","sheetName":"Eva - Module Template V1.0 - CoronaGo","tab":"Data Model","type":"Warning","problem":"Allowed values are missing for `Item`","solution":"For Data type Checkbox/CheckboxGroup/DropDown/RadioButton/Multiselect allowed values should be configured","rowIdx":"60","column":"7"},{"id":3,"sheetLink":"13zbPhkw6Wccwa9QPvUYFKEcEvLqHk9c9KY-9EQkMqo0","sheetName":"Eva - Module Template V1.0 - CoronaGo","tab":"Data Model","type":"Warning","problem":"Allowed values are missing for `Item`","solution":"For Data type Checkbox/CheckboxGroup/DropDown/RadioButton/Multiselect allowed values should be configured","rowIdx":"63","column":"7"},{"id":4,"sheetLink":"13zbPhkw6Wccwa9QPvUYFKEcEvLqHk9c9KY-9EQkMqo0","sheetName":"Eva - Module Template V1.0 - CoronaGo","tab":"Data Model","type":"Warning","problem":"Allowed values are missing for `Patient Hid`","solution":"For Data type Checkbox/CheckboxGroup/DropDown/RadioButton/Multiselect allowed values should be configured","rowIdx":"38","column":"7"},{"id":5,"sheetLink":"13zbPhkw6Wccwa9QPvUYFKEcEvLqHk9c9KY-9EQkMqo0","sheetName":"Eva - Module Template V1.0 - CoronaGo","tab":"Data Model","type":"Warning","problem":"Allowed values are missing for `Patient Name`","solution":"For Data type Checkbox/CheckboxGroup/DropDown/RadioButton/Multiselect allowed values should be configured","rowIdx":"39","column":"7"},{"id":6,"sheetLink":"13zbPhkw6Wccwa9QPvUYFKEcEvLqHk9c9KY-9EQkMqo0","sheetName":"Eva - Module Template V1.0 - CoronaGo","tab":"Data Model","type":"Warning","problem":"Allowed values are missing for `Meeting Id`","solution":"For Data type Checkbox/CheckboxGroup/DropDown/RadioButton/Multiselect allowed values should be configured","rowIdx":"41","column":"7"},{"id":7,"sheetLink":"13zbPhkw6Wccwa9QPvUYFKEcEvLqHk9c9KY-9EQkMqo0","sheetName":"Eva - Module Template V1.0 - CoronaGo","tab":"Data Model","type":"Warning","problem":"Allowed values are missing for `Doctor Id`","solution":"For Data type Checkbox/CheckboxGroup/DropDown/RadioButton/Multiselect allowed values should be configured","rowIdx":"42","column":"7"},{"id":8,"sheetLink":"13zbPhkw6Wccwa9QPvUYFKEcEvLqHk9c9KY-9EQkMqo0","sheetName":"Eva - Module Template V1.0 - CoronaGo","tab":"Data Model","type":"Warning","problem":"Allowed values are missing for `Doctor Name`","solution":"For Data type Checkbox/CheckboxGroup/DropDown/RadioButton/Multiselect allowed values should be configured","rowIdx":"43","column":"7"},{"id":9,"sheetLink":"13zbPhkw6Wccwa9QPvUYFKEcEvLqHk9c9KY-9EQkMqo0","sheetName":"Eva - Module Template V1.0 - CoronaGo","tab":"Data Model","type":"Warning","problem":"Allowed values are missing for `Meeting Status`","solution":"For Data type Checkbox/CheckboxGroup/DropDown/RadioButton/Multiselect allowed values should be configured","rowIdx":"47","column":"7"},{"id":10,"sheetLink":"13zbPhkw6Wccwa9QPvUYFKEcEvLqHk9c9KY-9EQkMqo0","sheetName":"Eva - Module Template V1.0 - CoronaGo","tab":"Data Model","type":"Warning","problem":"Allowed values are missing for `Meeting Url`","solution":"For Data type Checkbox/CheckboxGroup/DropDown/RadioButton/Multiselect allowed values should be configured","rowIdx":"48","column":"7"},{"id":11,"sheetLink":"13zbPhkw6Wccwa9QPvUYFKEcEvLqHk9c9KY-9EQkMqo0","sheetName":"Eva - Module Template V1.0 - CoronaGo","tab":"Data Model","type":"Warning","problem":"Allowed values are missing for `Doctor Name`","solution":"For Data type Checkbox/CheckboxGroup/DropDown/RadioButton/Multiselect allowed values should be configured","rowIdx":"52","column":"7"},{"id":12,"sheetLink":"13zbPhkw6Wccwa9QPvUYFKEcEvLqHk9c9KY-9EQkMqo0","sheetName":"Eva - Module Template V1.0 - CoronaGo","tab":"Data Model","type":"Warning","problem":"Allowed values are missing for `Item`","solution":"For Data type Checkbox/CheckboxGroup/DropDown/RadioButton/Multiselect allowed values should be configured","rowIdx":"56","column":"7"},{"id":13,"sheetLink":"13zbPhkw6Wccwa9QPvUYFKEcEvLqHk9c9KY-9EQkMqo0","sheetName":"Eva - Module Template V1.0 - CoronaGo","tab":"Data Model","type":"Warning","problem":"Allowed values are missing for `Patient Name`","solution":"For Data type Checkbox/CheckboxGroup/DropDown/RadioButton/Multiselect allowed values should be configured","rowIdx":"74","column":"7"},{"id":14,"sheetLink":"13zbPhkw6Wccwa9QPvUYFKEcEvLqHk9c9KY-9EQkMqo0","sheetName":"Eva - Module Template V1.0 - CoronaGo","tab":"Data Model","type":"Warning","problem":"Allowed values are missing for `Patient HId`","solution":"For Data type Checkbox/CheckboxGroup/DropDown/RadioButton/Multiselect allowed values should be configured","rowIdx":"76","column":"7"},{"id":15,"sheetLink":"13zbPhkw6Wccwa9QPvUYFKEcEvLqHk9c9KY-9EQkMqo0","sheetName":"Eva - Module Template V1.0 - CoronaGo","tab":"Data Model","type":"Warning","problem":"Allowed values are missing for `City`","solution":"For Data type Checkbox/CheckboxGroup/DropDown/RadioButton/Multiselect allowed values should be configured","rowIdx":"81","column":"7"},{"id":16,"sheetLink":"13zbPhkw6Wccwa9QPvUYFKEcEvLqHk9c9KY-9EQkMqo0","sheetName":"Eva - Module Template V1.0 - CoronaGo","tab":"Data Model","type":"Warning","problem":"Allowed values are missing for `Insurance Provider`","solution":"For Data type Checkbox/CheckboxGroup/DropDown/RadioButton/Multiselect allowed values should be configured","rowIdx":"83","column":"7"},{"id":17,"sheetLink":"13zbPhkw6Wccwa9QPvUYFKEcEvLqHk9c9KY-9EQkMqo0","sheetName":"Eva - Module Template V1.0 - CoronaGo","tab":"Data Model","type":"Warning","problem":"Allowed values are missing for `Patient Name`","solution":"For Data type Checkbox/CheckboxGroup/DropDown/RadioButton/Multiselect allowed values should be configured","rowIdx":"6","column":"7"},{"id":18,"sheetLink":"13zbPhkw6Wccwa9QPvUYFKEcEvLqHk9c9KY-9EQkMqo0","sheetName":"Eva - Module Template V1.0 - CoronaGo","tab":"Data Model","type":"Warning","problem":"Allowed values are missing for `Patient HId`","solution":"For Data type Checkbox/CheckboxGroup/DropDown/RadioButton/Multiselect allowed values should be configured","rowIdx":"8","column":"7"},{"id":19,"sheetLink":"13zbPhkw6Wccwa9QPvUYFKEcEvLqHk9c9KY-9EQkMqo0","sheetName":"Eva - Module Template V1.0 - CoronaGo","tab":"List Pages","type":"Warning","problem":"Column field `Date of Birth` not found in datamodel","solution":"Configure value for the column in list page","rowIdx":"4","column":"6"},{"id":20,"sheetLink":"13zbPhkw6Wccwa9QPvUYFKEcEvLqHk9c9KY-9EQkMqo0","sheetName":"Eva - Module Template V1.0 - CoronaGo","tab":"List Pages","type":"Warning","problem":"Column field `Date of Birth` not found in datamodel","solution":"Configure value for the column in list page","rowIdx":"4","column":"6"},{"id":21,"sheetLink":"13zbPhkw6Wccwa9QPvUYFKEcEvLqHk9c9KY-9EQkMqo0","sheetName":"Eva - Module Template V1.0 - CoronaGo","tab":"List Pages","type":"Warning","problem":"Column field `Date of Birth` not found in datamodel","solution":"Configure value for the column in list page","rowIdx":"5","column":"6"},{"id":22,"sheetLink":"13zbPhkw6Wccwa9QPvUYFKEcEvLqHk9c9KY-9EQkMqo0","sheetName":"Eva - Module Template V1.0 - CoronaGo","tab":"List Pages","type":"Warning","problem":"Column field `Date of Birth` not found in datamodel","solution":"Configure value for the column in list page","rowIdx":"5","column":"6"},{"id":23,"sheetLink":"13zbPhkw6Wccwa9QPvUYFKEcEvLqHk9c9KY-9EQkMqo0","sheetName":"Eva - Module Template V1.0 - CoronaGo","tab":"List Pages","type":"Warning","problem":"Column field `Date of Birth` not found in datamodel","solution":"Configure value for the column in list page","rowIdx":"6","column":"6"},{"id":24,"sheetLink":"13zbPhkw6Wccwa9QPvUYFKEcEvLqHk9c9KY-9EQkMqo0","sheetName":"Eva - Module Template V1.0 - CoronaGo","tab":"List Pages","type":"Warning","problem":"Column field `Date of Birth` not found in datamodel","solution":"Configure value for the column in list page","rowIdx":"6","column":"6"},{"id":25,"sheetLink":"13zbPhkw6Wccwa9QPvUYFKEcEvLqHk9c9KY-9EQkMqo0","sheetName":"Eva - Module Template V1.0 - CoronaGo","tab":"List Pages","type":"Warning","problem":"Column field `Date of Birth` not found in datamodel","solution":"Configure value for the column in list page","rowIdx":"7","column":"6"},{"id":26,"sheetLink":"13zbPhkw6Wccwa9QPvUYFKEcEvLqHk9c9KY-9EQkMqo0","sheetName":"Eva - Module Template V1.0 - CoronaGo","tab":"List Pages","type":"Warning","problem":"Column field `Date of Birth` not found in datamodel","solution":"Configure value for the column in list page","rowIdx":"7","column":"6"},{"id":27,"sheetLink":"13zbPhkw6Wccwa9QPvUYFKEcEvLqHk9c9KY-9EQkMqo0","sheetName":"Eva - Module Template V1.0 - CoronaGo","tab":"List Pages","type":"Warning","problem":"Column field `Date of Birth` not found in datamodel","solution":"Configure value for the column in list page","rowIdx":"8","column":"6"},{"id":28,"sheetLink":"13zbPhkw6Wccwa9QPvUYFKEcEvLqHk9c9KY-9EQkMqo0","sheetName":"Eva - Module Template V1.0 - CoronaGo","tab":"List Pages","type":"Warning","problem":"Column field `Date of Birth` not found in datamodel","solution":"Configure value for the column in list page","rowIdx":"8","column":"6"},{"id":29,"sheetLink":"13zbPhkw6Wccwa9QPvUYFKEcEvLqHk9c9KY-9EQkMqo0","sheetName":"Eva - Module Template V1.0 - CoronaGo","tab":"Data Model","type":"Warning","problem":"Allowed values are missing for `Hospital Name`","solution":"For Data type Checkbox/CheckboxGroup/DropDown/RadioButton/Multiselect allowed values should be configured","rowIdx":"45","column":"7"},{"id":30,"sheetLink":"13zbPhkw6Wccwa9QPvUYFKEcEvLqHk9c9KY-9EQkMqo0","sheetName":"Eva - Module Template V1.0 - CoronaGo","tab":"Data Model","type":"Warning","problem":"Allowed values are missing for `Item`","solution":"For Data type Checkbox/CheckboxGroup/DropDown/RadioButton/Multiselect allowed values should be configured","rowIdx":"46","column":"7"},{"id":31,"sheetLink":"13zbPhkw6Wccwa9QPvUYFKEcEvLqHk9c9KY-9EQkMqo0","sheetName":"Eva - Module Template V1.0 - CoronaGo","tab":"Data Model","type":"Warning","problem":"Allowed values are missing for `Item`","solution":"For Data type Checkbox/CheckboxGroup/DropDown/RadioButton/Multiselect allowed values should be configured","rowIdx":"49","column":"7"},{"id":32,"sheetLink":"13zbPhkw6Wccwa9QPvUYFKEcEvLqHk9c9KY-9EQkMqo0","sheetName":"Eva - Module Template V1.0 - CoronaGo","tab":"Data Model","type":"Warning","problem":"Allowed values are missing for `Patient Hid`","solution":"For Data type Checkbox/CheckboxGroup/DropDown/RadioButton/Multiselect allowed values should be configured","rowIdx":"24","column":"7"},{"id":33,"sheetLink":"13zbPhkw6Wccwa9QPvUYFKEcEvLqHk9c9KY-9EQkMqo0","sheetName":"Eva - Module Template V1.0 - CoronaGo","tab":"Data Model","type":"Warning","problem":"Allowed values are missing for `Patient Name`","solution":"For Data type Checkbox/CheckboxGroup/DropDown/RadioButton/Multiselect allowed values should be configured","rowIdx":"25","column":"7"},{"id":34,"sheetLink":"13zbPhkw6Wccwa9QPvUYFKEcEvLqHk9c9KY-9EQkMqo0","sheetName":"Eva - Module Template V1.0 - CoronaGo","tab":"Data Model","type":"Warning","problem":"Allowed values are missing for `Meeting Id`","solution":"For Data type Checkbox/CheckboxGroup/DropDown/RadioButton/Multiselect allowed values should be configured","rowIdx":"27","column":"7"},{"id":35,"sheetLink":"13zbPhkw6Wccwa9QPvUYFKEcEvLqHk9c9KY-9EQkMqo0","sheetName":"Eva - Module Template V1.0 - CoronaGo","tab":"Data Model","type":"Warning","problem":"Allowed values are missing for `Doctor Id`","solution":"For Data type Checkbox/CheckboxGroup/DropDown/RadioButton/Multiselect allowed values should be configured","rowIdx":"28","column":"7"},{"id":36,"sheetLink":"13zbPhkw6Wccwa9QPvUYFKEcEvLqHk9c9KY-9EQkMqo0","sheetName":"Eva - Module Template V1.0 - CoronaGo","tab":"Data Model","type":"Warning","problem":"Allowed values are missing for `Doctor Name`","solution":"For Data type Checkbox/CheckboxGroup/DropDown/RadioButton/Multiselect allowed values should be configured","rowIdx":"29","column":"7"},{"id":37,"sheetLink":"13zbPhkw6Wccwa9QPvUYFKEcEvLqHk9c9KY-9EQkMqo0","sheetName":"Eva - Module Template V1.0 - CoronaGo","tab":"Data Model","type":"Warning","problem":"Allowed values are missing for `Meeting Status`","solution":"For Data type Checkbox/CheckboxGroup/DropDown/RadioButton/Multiselect allowed values should be configured","rowIdx":"33","column":"7"},{"id":38,"sheetLink":"13zbPhkw6Wccwa9QPvUYFKEcEvLqHk9c9KY-9EQkMqo0","sheetName":"Eva - Module Template V1.0 - CoronaGo","tab":"Data Model","type":"Warning","problem":"Allowed values are missing for `Meeting Url`","solution":"For Data type Checkbox/CheckboxGroup/DropDown/RadioButton/Multiselect allowed values should be configured","rowIdx":"34","column":"7"},{"id":39,"sheetLink":"13zbPhkw6Wccwa9QPvUYFKEcEvLqHk9c9KY-9EQkMqo0","sheetName":"Eva - Module Template V1.0 - CoronaGo","tab":"Data Model","type":"Warning","problem":"Allowed values are missing for `Doctor Name`","solution":"For Data type Checkbox/CheckboxGroup/DropDown/RadioButton/Multiselect allowed values should be configured","rowIdx":"38","column":"7"},{"id":40,"sheetLink":"13zbPhkw6Wccwa9QPvUYFKEcEvLqHk9c9KY-9EQkMqo0","sheetName":"Eva - Module Template V1.0 - CoronaGo","tab":"Data Model","type":"Warning","problem":"Allowed values are missing for `Item`","solution":"For Data type Checkbox/CheckboxGroup/DropDown/RadioButton/Multiselect allowed values should be configured","rowIdx":"42","column":"7"},{"id":41,"sheetLink":"13zbPhkw6Wccwa9QPvUYFKEcEvLqHk9c9KY-9EQkMqo0","sheetName":"Eva - Module Template V1.0 - CoronaGo","tab":"Data Model","type":"Warning","problem":"Allowed values are missing for `Patient Name`","solution":"For Data type Checkbox/CheckboxGroup/DropDown/RadioButton/Multiselect allowed values should be configured","rowIdx":"60","column":"7"},{"id":42,"sheetLink":"13zbPhkw6Wccwa9QPvUYFKEcEvLqHk9c9KY-9EQkMqo0","sheetName":"Eva - Module Template V1.0 - CoronaGo","tab":"Data Model","type":"Warning","problem":"Allowed values are missing for `Patient HId`","solution":"For Data type Checkbox/CheckboxGroup/DropDown/RadioButton/Multiselect allowed values should be configured","rowIdx":"62","column":"7"},{"id":43,"sheetLink":"13zbPhkw6Wccwa9QPvUYFKEcEvLqHk9c9KY-9EQkMqo0","sheetName":"Eva - Module Template V1.0 - CoronaGo","tab":"Data Model","type":"Warning","problem":"Allowed values are missing for `City`","solution":"For Data type Checkbox/CheckboxGroup/DropDown/RadioButton/Multiselect allowed values should be configured","rowIdx":"67","column":"7"},{"id":44,"sheetLink":"13zbPhkw6Wccwa9QPvUYFKEcEvLqHk9c9KY-9EQkMqo0","sheetName":"Eva - Module Template V1.0 - CoronaGo","tab":"Data Model","type":"Warning","problem":"Allowed values are missing for `Insurance Provider`","solution":"For Data type Checkbox/CheckboxGroup/DropDown/RadioButton/Multiselect allowed values should be configured","rowIdx":"69","column":"7"},{"id":45,"sheetLink":"13zbPhkw6Wccwa9QPvUYFKEcEvLqHk9c9KY-9EQkMqo0","sheetName":"Eva - Module Template V1.0 - CoronaGo","tab":"Data Model","type":"Warning","problem":"Allowed values are missing for `Patient Name`","solution":"For Data type Checkbox/CheckboxGroup/DropDown/RadioButton/Multiselect allowed values should be configured","rowIdx":"6","column":"7"},{"id":46,"sheetLink":"13zbPhkw6Wccwa9QPvUYFKEcEvLqHk9c9KY-9EQkMqo0","sheetName":"Eva - Module Template V1.0 - CoronaGo","tab":"Data Model","type":"Warning","problem":"Allowed values are missing for `Patient HId`","solution":"For Data type Checkbox/CheckboxGroup/DropDown/RadioButton/Multiselect allowed values should be configured","rowIdx":"8","column":"7"},{"id":47,"sheetLink":"13zbPhkw6Wccwa9QPvUYFKEcEvLqHk9c9KY-9EQkMqo0","sheetName":"Eva - Module Template V1.0 - CoronaGo","tab":"List Pages","type":"Warning","problem":"Column field `Date of Birth` not found in datamodel","solution":"Configure value for the column in list page","rowIdx":"4","column":"6"},{"id":48,"sheetLink":"13zbPhkw6Wccwa9QPvUYFKEcEvLqHk9c9KY-9EQkMqo0","sheetName":"Eva - Module Template V1.0 - CoronaGo","tab":"List Pages","type":"Warning","problem":"Column field `Date of Birth` not found in datamodel","solution":"Configure value for the column in list page","rowIdx":"4","column":"6"},{"id":49,"sheetLink":"13zbPhkw6Wccwa9QPvUYFKEcEvLqHk9c9KY-9EQkMqo0","sheetName":"Eva - Module Template V1.0 - CoronaGo","tab":"List Pages","type":"Warning","problem":"Column field `Date of Birth` not found in datamodel","solution":"Configure value for the column in list page","rowIdx":"5","column":"6"},{"id":50,"sheetLink":"13zbPhkw6Wccwa9QPvUYFKEcEvLqHk9c9KY-9EQkMqo0","sheetName":"Eva - Module Template V1.0 - CoronaGo","tab":"List Pages","type":"Warning","problem":"Column field `Date of Birth` not found in datamodel","solution":"Configure value for the column in list page","rowIdx":"5","column":"6"},{"id":51,"sheetLink":"13zbPhkw6Wccwa9QPvUYFKEcEvLqHk9c9KY-9EQkMqo0","sheetName":"Eva - Module Template V1.0 - CoronaGo","tab":"List Pages","type":"Warning","problem":"Column field `Date of Birth` not found in datamodel","solution":"Configure value for the column in list page","rowIdx":"6","column":"6"},{"id":52,"sheetLink":"13zbPhkw6Wccwa9QPvUYFKEcEvLqHk9c9KY-9EQkMqo0","sheetName":"Eva - Module Template V1.0 - CoronaGo","tab":"List Pages","type":"Warning","problem":"Column field `Date of Birth` not found in datamodel","solution":"Configure value for the column in list page","rowIdx":"6","column":"6"},{"id":53,"sheetLink":"13zbPhkw6Wccwa9QPvUYFKEcEvLqHk9c9KY-9EQkMqo0","sheetName":"Eva - Module Template V1.0 - CoronaGo","tab":"List Pages","type":"Warning","problem":"Column field `Date of Birth` not found in datamodel","solution":"Configure value for the column in list page","rowIdx":"7","column":"6"},{"id":54,"sheetLink":"13zbPhkw6Wccwa9QPvUYFKEcEvLqHk9c9KY-9EQkMqo0","sheetName":"Eva - Module Template V1.0 - CoronaGo","tab":"List Pages","type":"Warning","problem":"Column field `Date of Birth` not found in datamodel","solution":"Configure value for the column in list page","rowIdx":"7","column":"6"},{"id":55,"sheetLink":"13zbPhkw6Wccwa9QPvUYFKEcEvLqHk9c9KY-9EQkMqo0","sheetName":"Eva - Module Template V1.0 - CoronaGo","tab":"List Pages","type":"Warning","problem":"Column field `Date of Birth` not found in datamodel","solution":"Configure value for the column in list page","rowIdx":"8","column":"6"},{"id":56,"sheetLink":"13zbPhkw6Wccwa9QPvUYFKEcEvLqHk9c9KY-9EQkMqo0","sheetName":"Eva - Module Template V1.0 - CoronaGo","tab":"List Pages","type":"Warning","problem":"Column field `Date of Birth` not found in datamodel","solution":"Configure value for the column in list page","rowIdx":"8","column":"6"}]},{"id":2,"action":"Detail Page Generation","dateTime":1585123792335,"items":[{"id":1,"sheetLink":"13zbPhkw6Wccwa9QPvUYFKEcEvLqHk9c9KY-9EQkMqo0","sheetName":"Eva - Module Template V1.0 - CoronaGo","tab":"Data Model","type":"Warning","problem":"Allowed values are missing for `Hospital Name`","solution":"For Data type Checkbox/CheckboxGroup/DropDown/RadioButton/Multiselect allowed values should be configured","rowIdx":"59","column":"7"},{"id":2,"sheetLink":"13zbPhkw6Wccwa9QPvUYFKEcEvLqHk9c9KY-9EQkMqo0","sheetName":"Eva - Module Template V1.0 - CoronaGo","tab":"Data Model","type":"Warning","problem":"Allowed values are missing for `Item`","solution":"For Data type Checkbox/CheckboxGroup/DropDown/RadioButton/Multiselect allowed values should be configured","rowIdx":"60","column":"7"},{"id":3,"sheetLink":"13zbPhkw6Wccwa9QPvUYFKEcEvLqHk9c9KY-9EQkMqo0","sheetName":"Eva - Module Template V1.0 - CoronaGo","tab":"Data Model","type":"Warning","problem":"Allowed values are missing for `Item`","solution":"For Data type Checkbox/CheckboxGroup/DropDown/RadioButton/Multiselect allowed values should be configured","rowIdx":"63","column":"7"},{"id":4,"sheetLink":"13zbPhkw6Wccwa9QPvUYFKEcEvLqHk9c9KY-9EQkMqo0","sheetName":"Eva - Module Template V1.0 - CoronaGo","tab":"Data Model","type":"Warning","problem":"Allowed values are missing for `Patient Hid`","solution":"For Data type Checkbox/CheckboxGroup/DropDown/RadioButton/Multiselect allowed values should be configured","rowIdx":"38","column":"7"},{"id":5,"sheetLink":"13zbPhkw6Wccwa9QPvUYFKEcEvLqHk9c9KY-9EQkMqo0","sheetName":"Eva - Module Template V1.0 - CoronaGo","tab":"Data Model","type":"Warning","problem":"Allowed values are missing for `Patient Name`","solution":"For Data type Checkbox/CheckboxGroup/DropDown/RadioButton/Multiselect allowed values should be configured","rowIdx":"39","column":"7"},{"id":6,"sheetLink":"13zbPhkw6Wccwa9QPvUYFKEcEvLqHk9c9KY-9EQkMqo0","sheetName":"Eva - Module Template V1.0 - CoronaGo","tab":"Data Model","type":"Warning","problem":"Allowed values are missing for `Meeting Id`","solution":"For Data type Checkbox/CheckboxGroup/DropDown/RadioButton/Multiselect allowed values should be configured","rowIdx":"41","column":"7"},{"id":7,"sheetLink":"13zbPhkw6Wccwa9QPvUYFKEcEvLqHk9c9KY-9EQkMqo0","sheetName":"Eva - Module Template V1.0 - CoronaGo","tab":"Data Model","type":"Warning","problem":"Allowed values are missing for `Doctor Id`","solution":"For Data type Checkbox/CheckboxGroup/DropDown/RadioButton/Multiselect allowed values should be configured","rowIdx":"42","column":"7"},{"id":8,"sheetLink":"13zbPhkw6Wccwa9QPvUYFKEcEvLqHk9c9KY-9EQkMqo0","sheetName":"Eva - Module Template V1.0 - CoronaGo","tab":"Data Model","type":"Warning","problem":"Allowed values are missing for `Doctor Name`","solution":"For Data type Checkbox/CheckboxGroup/DropDown/RadioButton/Multiselect allowed values should be configured","rowIdx":"43","column":"7"},{"id":9,"sheetLink":"13zbPhkw6Wccwa9QPvUYFKEcEvLqHk9c9KY-9EQkMqo0","sheetName":"Eva - Module Template V1.0 - CoronaGo","tab":"Data Model","type":"Warning","problem":"Allowed values are missing for `Meeting Status`","solution":"For Data type Checkbox/CheckboxGroup/DropDown/RadioButton/Multiselect allowed values should be configured","rowIdx":"47","column":"7"},{"id":10,"sheetLink":"13zbPhkw6Wccwa9QPvUYFKEcEvLqHk9c9KY-9EQkMqo0","sheetName":"Eva - Module Template V1.0 - CoronaGo","tab":"Data Model","type":"Warning","problem":"Allowed values are missing for `Meeting Url`","solution":"For Data type Checkbox/CheckboxGroup/DropDown/RadioButton/Multiselect allowed values should be configured","rowIdx":"48","column":"7"},{"id":11,"sheetLink":"13zbPhkw6Wccwa9QPvUYFKEcEvLqHk9c9KY-9EQkMqo0","sheetName":"Eva - Module Template V1.0 - CoronaGo","tab":"Data Model","type":"Warning","problem":"Allowed values are missing for `Doctor Name`","solution":"For Data type Checkbox/CheckboxGroup/DropDown/RadioButton/Multiselect allowed values should be configured","rowIdx":"52","column":"7"},{"id":12,"sheetLink":"13zbPhkw6Wccwa9QPvUYFKEcEvLqHk9c9KY-9EQkMqo0","sheetName":"Eva - Module Template V1.0 - CoronaGo","tab":"Data Model","type":"Warning","problem":"Allowed values are missing for `Item`","solution":"For Data type Checkbox/CheckboxGroup/DropDown/RadioButton/Multiselect allowed values should be configured","rowIdx":"56","column":"7"},{"id":13,"sheetLink":"13zbPhkw6Wccwa9QPvUYFKEcEvLqHk9c9KY-9EQkMqo0","sheetName":"Eva - Module Template V1.0 - CoronaGo","tab":"Data Model","type":"Warning","problem":"Allowed values are missing for `Patient Name`","solution":"For Data type Checkbox/CheckboxGroup/DropDown/RadioButton/Multiselect allowed values should be configured","rowIdx":"74","column":"7"},{"id":14,"sheetLink":"13zbPhkw6Wccwa9QPvUYFKEcEvLqHk9c9KY-9EQkMqo0","sheetName":"Eva - Module Template V1.0 - CoronaGo","tab":"Data Model","type":"Warning","problem":"Allowed values are missing for `Patient HId`","solution":"For Data type Checkbox/CheckboxGroup/DropDown/RadioButton/Multiselect allowed values should be configured","rowIdx":"76","column":"7"},{"id":15,"sheetLink":"13zbPhkw6Wccwa9QPvUYFKEcEvLqHk9c9KY-9EQkMqo0","sheetName":"Eva - Module Template V1.0 - CoronaGo","tab":"Data Model","type":"Warning","problem":"Allowed values are missing for `City`","solution":"For Data type Checkbox/CheckboxGroup/DropDown/RadioButton/Multiselect allowed values should be configured","rowIdx":"81","column":"7"},{"id":16,"sheetLink":"13zbPhkw6Wccwa9QPvUYFKEcEvLqHk9c9KY-9EQkMqo0","sheetName":"Eva - Module Template V1.0 - CoronaGo","tab":"Data Model","type":"Warning","problem":"Allowed values are missing for `Insurance Provider`","solution":"For Data type Checkbox/CheckboxGroup/DropDown/RadioButton/Multiselect allowed values should be configured","rowIdx":"83","column":"7"},{"id":17,"sheetLink":"13zbPhkw6Wccwa9QPvUYFKEcEvLqHk9c9KY-9EQkMqo0","sheetName":"Eva - Module Template V1.0 - CoronaGo","tab":"Data Model","type":"Warning","problem":"Allowed values are missing for `Patient Name`","solution":"For Data type Checkbox/CheckboxGroup/DropDown/RadioButton/Multiselect allowed values should be configured","rowIdx":"6","column":"7"},{"id":18,"sheetLink":"13zbPhkw6Wccwa9QPvUYFKEcEvLqHk9c9KY-9EQkMqo0","sheetName":"Eva - Module Template V1.0 - CoronaGo","tab":"Data Model","type":"Warning","problem":"Allowed values are missing for `Patient HId`","solution":"For Data type Checkbox/CheckboxGroup/DropDown/RadioButton/Multiselect allowed values should be configured","rowIdx":"8","column":"7"},{"id":19,"sheetLink":"13zbPhkw6Wccwa9QPvUYFKEcEvLqHk9c9KY-9EQkMqo0","sheetName":"Eva - Module Template V1.0 - CoronaGo","tab":"List Pages","type":"Warning","problem":"Column field `Date of Birth` not found in datamodel","solution":"Configure value for the column in list page","rowIdx":"4","column":"6"},{"id":20,"sheetLink":"13zbPhkw6Wccwa9QPvUYFKEcEvLqHk9c9KY-9EQkMqo0","sheetName":"Eva - Module Template V1.0 - CoronaGo","tab":"List Pages","type":"Warning","problem":"Column field `Date of Birth` not found in datamodel","solution":"Configure value for the column in list page","rowIdx":"4","column":"6"},{"id":21,"sheetLink":"13zbPhkw6Wccwa9QPvUYFKEcEvLqHk9c9KY-9EQkMqo0","sheetName":"Eva - Module Template V1.0 - CoronaGo","tab":"List Pages","type":"Warning","problem":"Column field `Date of Birth` not found in datamodel","solution":"Configure value for the column in list page","rowIdx":"5","column":"6"},{"id":22,"sheetLink":"13zbPhkw6Wccwa9QPvUYFKEcEvLqHk9c9KY-9EQkMqo0","sheetName":"Eva - Module Template V1.0 - CoronaGo","tab":"List Pages","type":"Warning","problem":"Column field `Date of Birth` not found in datamodel","solution":"Configure value for the column in list page","rowIdx":"5","column":"6"},{"id":23,"sheetLink":"13zbPhkw6Wccwa9QPvUYFKEcEvLqHk9c9KY-9EQkMqo0","sheetName":"Eva - Module Template V1.0 - CoronaGo","tab":"List Pages","type":"Warning","problem":"Column field `Date of Birth` not found in datamodel","solution":"Configure value for the column in list page","rowIdx":"6","column":"6"},{"id":24,"sheetLink":"13zbPhkw6Wccwa9QPvUYFKEcEvLqHk9c9KY-9EQkMqo0","sheetName":"Eva - Module Template V1.0 - CoronaGo","tab":"List Pages","type":"Warning","problem":"Column field `Date of Birth` not found in datamodel","solution":"Configure value for the column in list page","rowIdx":"6","column":"6"},{"id":25,"sheetLink":"13zbPhkw6Wccwa9QPvUYFKEcEvLqHk9c9KY-9EQkMqo0","sheetName":"Eva - Module Template V1.0 - CoronaGo","tab":"List Pages","type":"Warning","problem":"Column field `Date of Birth` not found in datamodel","solution":"Configure value for the column in list page","rowIdx":"7","column":"6"},{"id":26,"sheetLink":"13zbPhkw6Wccwa9QPvUYFKEcEvLqHk9c9KY-9EQkMqo0","sheetName":"Eva - Module Template V1.0 - CoronaGo","tab":"List Pages","type":"Warning","problem":"Column field `Date of Birth` not found in datamodel","solution":"Configure value for the column in list page","rowIdx":"7","column":"6"},{"id":27,"sheetLink":"13zbPhkw6Wccwa9QPvUYFKEcEvLqHk9c9KY-9EQkMqo0","sheetName":"Eva - Module Template V1.0 - CoronaGo","tab":"List Pages","type":"Warning","problem":"Column field `Date of Birth` not found in datamodel","solution":"Configure value for the column in list page","rowIdx":"8","column":"6"},{"id":28,"sheetLink":"13zbPhkw6Wccwa9QPvUYFKEcEvLqHk9c9KY-9EQkMqo0","sheetName":"Eva - Module Template V1.0 - CoronaGo","tab":"List Pages","type":"Warning","problem":"Column field `Date of Birth` not found in datamodel","solution":"Configure value for the column in list page","rowIdx":"8","column":"6"},{"id":29,"sheetLink":"13zbPhkw6Wccwa9QPvUYFKEcEvLqHk9c9KY-9EQkMqo0","sheetName":"Eva - Module Template V1.0 - CoronaGo","tab":"Data Model","type":"Warning","problem":"Allowed values are missing for `Hospital Name`","solution":"For Data type Checkbox/CheckboxGroup/DropDown/RadioButton/Multiselect allowed values should be configured","rowIdx":"45","column":"7"},{"id":30,"sheetLink":"13zbPhkw6Wccwa9QPvUYFKEcEvLqHk9c9KY-9EQkMqo0","sheetName":"Eva - Module Template V1.0 - CoronaGo","tab":"Data Model","type":"Warning","problem":"Allowed values are missing for `Item`","solution":"For Data type Checkbox/CheckboxGroup/DropDown/RadioButton/Multiselect allowed values should be configured","rowIdx":"46","column":"7"},{"id":31,"sheetLink":"13zbPhkw6Wccwa9QPvUYFKEcEvLqHk9c9KY-9EQkMqo0","sheetName":"Eva - Module Template V1.0 - CoronaGo","tab":"Data Model","type":"Warning","problem":"Allowed values are missing for `Item`","solution":"For Data type Checkbox/CheckboxGroup/DropDown/RadioButton/Multiselect allowed values should be configured","rowIdx":"49","column":"7"},{"id":32,"sheetLink":"13zbPhkw6Wccwa9QPvUYFKEcEvLqHk9c9KY-9EQkMqo0","sheetName":"Eva - Module Template V1.0 - CoronaGo","tab":"Data Model","type":"Warning","problem":"Allowed values are missing for `Patient Hid`","solution":"For Data type Checkbox/CheckboxGroup/DropDown/RadioButton/Multiselect allowed values should be configured","rowIdx":"24","column":"7"},{"id":33,"sheetLink":"13zbPhkw6Wccwa9QPvUYFKEcEvLqHk9c9KY-9EQkMqo0","sheetName":"Eva - Module Template V1.0 - CoronaGo","tab":"Data Model","type":"Warning","problem":"Allowed values are missing for `Patient Name`","solution":"For Data type Checkbox/CheckboxGroup/DropDown/RadioButton/Multiselect allowed values should be configured","rowIdx":"25","column":"7"},{"id":34,"sheetLink":"13zbPhkw6Wccwa9QPvUYFKEcEvLqHk9c9KY-9EQkMqo0","sheetName":"Eva - Module Template V1.0 - CoronaGo","tab":"Data Model","type":"Warning","problem":"Allowed values are missing for `Meeting Id`","solution":"For Data type Checkbox/CheckboxGroup/DropDown/RadioButton/Multiselect allowed values should be configured","rowIdx":"27","column":"7"},{"id":35,"sheetLink":"13zbPhkw6Wccwa9QPvUYFKEcEvLqHk9c9KY-9EQkMqo0","sheetName":"Eva - Module Template V1.0 - CoronaGo","tab":"Data Model","type":"Warning","problem":"Allowed values are missing for `Doctor Id`","solution":"For Data type Checkbox/CheckboxGroup/DropDown/RadioButton/Multiselect allowed values should be configured","rowIdx":"28","column":"7"},{"id":36,"sheetLink":"13zbPhkw6Wccwa9QPvUYFKEcEvLqHk9c9KY-9EQkMqo0","sheetName":"Eva - Module Template V1.0 - CoronaGo","tab":"Data Model","type":"Warning","problem":"Allowed values are missing for `Doctor Name`","solution":"For Data type Checkbox/CheckboxGroup/DropDown/RadioButton/Multiselect allowed values should be configured","rowIdx":"29","column":"7"},{"id":37,"sheetLink":"13zbPhkw6Wccwa9QPvUYFKEcEvLqHk9c9KY-9EQkMqo0","sheetName":"Eva - Module Template V1.0 - CoronaGo","tab":"Data Model","type":"Warning","problem":"Allowed values are missing for `Meeting Status`","solution":"For Data type Checkbox/CheckboxGroup/DropDown/RadioButton/Multiselect allowed values should be configured","rowIdx":"33","column":"7"},{"id":38,"sheetLink":"13zbPhkw6Wccwa9QPvUYFKEcEvLqHk9c9KY-9EQkMqo0","sheetName":"Eva - Module Template V1.0 - CoronaGo","tab":"Data Model","type":"Warning","problem":"Allowed values are missing for `Meeting Url`","solution":"For Data type Checkbox/CheckboxGroup/DropDown/RadioButton/Multiselect allowed values should be configured","rowIdx":"34","column":"7"},{"id":39,"sheetLink":"13zbPhkw6Wccwa9QPvUYFKEcEvLqHk9c9KY-9EQkMqo0","sheetName":"Eva - Module Template V1.0 - CoronaGo","tab":"Data Model","type":"Warning","problem":"Allowed values are missing for `Doctor Name`","solution":"For Data type Checkbox/CheckboxGroup/DropDown/RadioButton/Multiselect allowed values should be configured","rowIdx":"38","column":"7"},{"id":40,"sheetLink":"13zbPhkw6Wccwa9QPvUYFKEcEvLqHk9c9KY-9EQkMqo0","sheetName":"Eva - Module Template V1.0 - CoronaGo","tab":"Data Model","type":"Warning","problem":"Allowed values are missing for `Item`","solution":"For Data type Checkbox/CheckboxGroup/DropDown/RadioButton/Multiselect allowed values should be configured","rowIdx":"42","column":"7"},{"id":41,"sheetLink":"13zbPhkw6Wccwa9QPvUYFKEcEvLqHk9c9KY-9EQkMqo0","sheetName":"Eva - Module Template V1.0 - CoronaGo","tab":"Data Model","type":"Warning","problem":"Allowed values are missing for `Patient Name`","solution":"For Data type Checkbox/CheckboxGroup/DropDown/RadioButton/Multiselect allowed values should be configured","rowIdx":"60","column":"7"},{"id":42,"sheetLink":"13zbPhkw6Wccwa9QPvUYFKEcEvLqHk9c9KY-9EQkMqo0","sheetName":"Eva - Module Template V1.0 - CoronaGo","tab":"Data Model","type":"Warning","problem":"Allowed values are missing for `Patient HId`","solution":"For Data type Checkbox/CheckboxGroup/DropDown/RadioButton/Multiselect allowed values should be configured","rowIdx":"62","column":"7"},{"id":43,"sheetLink":"13zbPhkw6Wccwa9QPvUYFKEcEvLqHk9c9KY-9EQkMqo0","sheetName":"Eva - Module Template V1.0 - CoronaGo","tab":"Data Model","type":"Warning","problem":"Allowed values are missing for `City`","solution":"For Data type Checkbox/CheckboxGroup/DropDown/RadioButton/Multiselect allowed values should be configured","rowIdx":"67","column":"7"},{"id":44,"sheetLink":"13zbPhkw6Wccwa9QPvUYFKEcEvLqHk9c9KY-9EQkMqo0","sheetName":"Eva - Module Template V1.0 - CoronaGo","tab":"Data Model","type":"Warning","problem":"Allowed values are missing for `Insurance Provider`","solution":"For Data type Checkbox/CheckboxGroup/DropDown/RadioButton/Multiselect allowed values should be configured","rowIdx":"69","column":"7"},{"id":45,"sheetLink":"13zbPhkw6Wccwa9QPvUYFKEcEvLqHk9c9KY-9EQkMqo0","sheetName":"Eva - Module Template V1.0 - CoronaGo","tab":"Data Model","type":"Warning","problem":"Allowed values are missing for `Patient Name`","solution":"For Data type Checkbox/CheckboxGroup/DropDown/RadioButton/Multiselect allowed values should be configured","rowIdx":"6","column":"7"},{"id":46,"sheetLink":"13zbPhkw6Wccwa9QPvUYFKEcEvLqHk9c9KY-9EQkMqo0","sheetName":"Eva - Module Template V1.0 - CoronaGo","tab":"Data Model","type":"Warning","problem":"Allowed values are missing for `Patient HId`","solution":"For Data type Checkbox/CheckboxGroup/DropDown/RadioButton/Multiselect allowed values should be configured","rowIdx":"8","column":"7"},{"id":47,"sheetLink":"13zbPhkw6Wccwa9QPvUYFKEcEvLqHk9c9KY-9EQkMqo0","sheetName":"Eva - Module Template V1.0 - CoronaGo","tab":"List Pages","type":"Warning","problem":"Column field `Date of Birth` not found in datamodel","solution":"Configure value for the column in list page","rowIdx":"4","column":"6"},{"id":48,"sheetLink":"13zbPhkw6Wccwa9QPvUYFKEcEvLqHk9c9KY-9EQkMqo0","sheetName":"Eva - Module Template V1.0 - CoronaGo","tab":"List Pages","type":"Warning","problem":"Column field `Date of Birth` not found in datamodel","solution":"Configure value for the column in list page","rowIdx":"4","column":"6"},{"id":49,"sheetLink":"13zbPhkw6Wccwa9QPvUYFKEcEvLqHk9c9KY-9EQkMqo0","sheetName":"Eva - Module Template V1.0 - CoronaGo","tab":"List Pages","type":"Warning","problem":"Column field `Date of Birth` not found in datamodel","solution":"Configure value for the column in list page","rowIdx":"5","column":"6"},{"id":50,"sheetLink":"13zbPhkw6Wccwa9QPvUYFKEcEvLqHk9c9KY-9EQkMqo0","sheetName":"Eva - Module Template V1.0 - CoronaGo","tab":"List Pages","type":"Warning","problem":"Column field `Date of Birth` not found in datamodel","solution":"Configure value for the column in list page","rowIdx":"5","column":"6"},{"id":51,"sheetLink":"13zbPhkw6Wccwa9QPvUYFKEcEvLqHk9c9KY-9EQkMqo0","sheetName":"Eva - Module Template V1.0 - CoronaGo","tab":"List Pages","type":"Warning","problem":"Column field `Date of Birth` not found in datamodel","solution":"Configure value for the column in list page","rowIdx":"6","column":"6"},{"id":52,"sheetLink":"13zbPhkw6Wccwa9QPvUYFKEcEvLqHk9c9KY-9EQkMqo0","sheetName":"Eva - Module Template V1.0 - CoronaGo","tab":"List Pages","type":"Warning","problem":"Column field `Date of Birth` not found in datamodel","solution":"Configure value for the column in list page","rowIdx":"6","column":"6"},{"id":53,"sheetLink":"13zbPhkw6Wccwa9QPvUYFKEcEvLqHk9c9KY-9EQkMqo0","sheetName":"Eva - Module Template V1.0 - CoronaGo","tab":"List Pages","type":"Warning","problem":"Column field `Date of Birth` not found in datamodel","solution":"Configure value for the column in list page","rowIdx":"7","column":"6"},{"id":54,"sheetLink":"13zbPhkw6Wccwa9QPvUYFKEcEvLqHk9c9KY-9EQkMqo0","sheetName":"Eva - Module Template V1.0 - CoronaGo","tab":"List Pages","type":"Warning","problem":"Column field `Date of Birth` not found in datamodel","solution":"Configure value for the column in list page","rowIdx":"7","column":"6"},{"id":55,"sheetLink":"13zbPhkw6Wccwa9QPvUYFKEcEvLqHk9c9KY-9EQkMqo0","sheetName":"Eva - Module Template V1.0 - CoronaGo","tab":"List Pages","type":"Warning","problem":"Column field `Date of Birth` not found in datamodel","solution":"Configure value for the column in list page","rowIdx":"8","column":"6"},{"id":56,"sheetLink":"13zbPhkw6Wccwa9QPvUYFKEcEvLqHk9c9KY-9EQkMqo0","sheetName":"Eva - Module Template V1.0 - CoronaGo","tab":"List Pages","type":"Warning","problem":"Column field `Date of Birth` not found in datamodel","solution":"Configure value for the column in list page","rowIdx":"8","column":"6"}]},{"id":3,"action":"List Page Generation","dateTime":1585123750370,"items":[{"id":1,"sheetLink":"13zbPhkw6Wccwa9QPvUYFKEcEvLqHk9c9KY-9EQkMqo0","sheetName":"Eva - Module Template V1.0 - CoronaGo","tab":"Data Model","type":"Warning","problem":"Allowed values are missing for `Hospital Name`","solution":"For Data type Checkbox/CheckboxGroup/DropDown/RadioButton/Multiselect allowed values should be configured","rowIdx":"59","column":"7"},{"id":2,"sheetLink":"13zbPhkw6Wccwa9QPvUYFKEcEvLqHk9c9KY-9EQkMqo0","sheetName":"Eva - Module Template V1.0 - CoronaGo","tab":"Data Model","type":"Warning","problem":"Allowed values are missing for `Item`","solution":"For Data type Checkbox/CheckboxGroup/DropDown/RadioButton/Multiselect allowed values should be configured","rowIdx":"60","column":"7"},{"id":3,"sheetLink":"13zbPhkw6Wccwa9QPvUYFKEcEvLqHk9c9KY-9EQkMqo0","sheetName":"Eva - Module Template V1.0 - CoronaGo","tab":"Data Model","type":"Warning","problem":"Allowed values are missing for `Item`","solution":"For Data type Checkbox/CheckboxGroup/DropDown/RadioButton/Multiselect allowed values should be configured","rowIdx":"63","column":"7"},{"id":4,"sheetLink":"13zbPhkw6Wccwa9QPvUYFKEcEvLqHk9c9KY-9EQkMqo0","sheetName":"Eva - Module Template V1.0 - CoronaGo","tab":"Data Model","type":"Warning","problem":"Allowed values are missing for `Patient Hid`","solution":"For Data type Checkbox/CheckboxGroup/DropDown/RadioButton/Multiselect allowed values should be configured","rowIdx":"38","column":"7"},{"id":5,"sheetLink":"13zbPhkw6Wccwa9QPvUYFKEcEvLqHk9c9KY-9EQkMqo0","sheetName":"Eva - Module Template V1.0 - CoronaGo","tab":"Data Model","type":"Warning","problem":"Allowed values are missing for `Patient Name`","solution":"For Data type Checkbox/CheckboxGroup/DropDown/RadioButton/Multiselect allowed values should be configured","rowIdx":"39","column":"7"},{"id":6,"sheetLink":"13zbPhkw6Wccwa9QPvUYFKEcEvLqHk9c9KY-9EQkMqo0","sheetName":"Eva - Module Template V1.0 - CoronaGo","tab":"Data Model","type":"Warning","problem":"Allowed values are missing for `Meeting Id`","solution":"For Data type Checkbox/CheckboxGroup/DropDown/RadioButton/Multiselect allowed values should be configured","rowIdx":"41","column":"7"},{"id":7,"sheetLink":"13zbPhkw6Wccwa9QPvUYFKEcEvLqHk9c9KY-9EQkMqo0","sheetName":"Eva - Module Template V1.0 - CoronaGo","tab":"Data Model","type":"Warning","problem":"Allowed values are missing for `Doctor Id`","solution":"For Data type Checkbox/CheckboxGroup/DropDown/RadioButton/Multiselect allowed values should be configured","rowIdx":"42","column":"7"},{"id":8,"sheetLink":"13zbPhkw6Wccwa9QPvUYFKEcEvLqHk9c9KY-9EQkMqo0","sheetName":"Eva - Module Template V1.0 - CoronaGo","tab":"Data Model","type":"Warning","problem":"Allowed values are missing for `Doctor Name`","solution":"For Data type Checkbox/CheckboxGroup/DropDown/RadioButton/Multiselect allowed values should be configured","rowIdx":"43","column":"7"},{"id":9,"sheetLink":"13zbPhkw6Wccwa9QPvUYFKEcEvLqHk9c9KY-9EQkMqo0","sheetName":"Eva - Module Template V1.0 - CoronaGo","tab":"Data Model","type":"Warning","problem":"Allowed values are missing for `Meeting Status`","solution":"For Data type Checkbox/CheckboxGroup/DropDown/RadioButton/Multiselect allowed values should be configured","rowIdx":"47","column":"7"},{"id":10,"sheetLink":"13zbPhkw6Wccwa9QPvUYFKEcEvLqHk9c9KY-9EQkMqo0","sheetName":"Eva - Module Template V1.0 - CoronaGo","tab":"Data Model","type":"Warning","problem":"Allowed values are missing for `Meeting Url`","solution":"For Data type Checkbox/CheckboxGroup/DropDown/RadioButton/Multiselect allowed values should be configured","rowIdx":"48","column":"7"},{"id":11,"sheetLink":"13zbPhkw6Wccwa9QPvUYFKEcEvLqHk9c9KY-9EQkMqo0","sheetName":"Eva - Module Template V1.0 - CoronaGo","tab":"Data Model","type":"Warning","problem":"Allowed values are missing for `Doctor Name`","solution":"For Data type Checkbox/CheckboxGroup/DropDown/RadioButton/Multiselect allowed values should be configured","rowIdx":"52","column":"7"},{"id":12,"sheetLink":"13zbPhkw6Wccwa9QPvUYFKEcEvLqHk9c9KY-9EQkMqo0","sheetName":"Eva - Module Template V1.0 - CoronaGo","tab":"Data Model","type":"Warning","problem":"Allowed values are missing for `Item`","solution":"For Data type Checkbox/CheckboxGroup/DropDown/RadioButton/Multiselect allowed values should be configured","rowIdx":"56","column":"7"},{"id":13,"sheetLink":"13zbPhkw6Wccwa9QPvUYFKEcEvLqHk9c9KY-9EQkMqo0","sheetName":"Eva - Module Template V1.0 - CoronaGo","tab":"Data Model","type":"Warning","problem":"Allowed values are missing for `Patient Name`","solution":"For Data type Checkbox/CheckboxGroup/DropDown/RadioButton/Multiselect allowed values should be configured","rowIdx":"74","column":"7"},{"id":14,"sheetLink":"13zbPhkw6Wccwa9QPvUYFKEcEvLqHk9c9KY-9EQkMqo0","sheetName":"Eva - Module Template V1.0 - CoronaGo","tab":"Data Model","type":"Warning","problem":"Allowed values are missing for `Patient HId`","solution":"For Data type Checkbox/CheckboxGroup/DropDown/RadioButton/Multiselect allowed values should be configured","rowIdx":"76","column":"7"},{"id":15,"sheetLink":"13zbPhkw6Wccwa9QPvUYFKEcEvLqHk9c9KY-9EQkMqo0","sheetName":"Eva - Module Template V1.0 - CoronaGo","tab":"Data Model","type":"Warning","problem":"Allowed values are missing for `City`","solution":"For Data type Checkbox/CheckboxGroup/DropDown/RadioButton/Multiselect allowed values should be configured","rowIdx":"81","column":"7"},{"id":16,"sheetLink":"13zbPhkw6Wccwa9QPvUYFKEcEvLqHk9c9KY-9EQkMqo0","sheetName":"Eva - Module Template V1.0 - CoronaGo","tab":"Data Model","type":"Warning","problem":"Allowed values are missing for `Insurance Provider`","solution":"For Data type Checkbox/CheckboxGroup/DropDown/RadioButton/Multiselect allowed values should be configured","rowIdx":"83","column":"7"},{"id":17,"sheetLink":"13zbPhkw6Wccwa9QPvUYFKEcEvLqHk9c9KY-9EQkMqo0","sheetName":"Eva - Module Template V1.0 - CoronaGo","tab":"Data Model","type":"Warning","problem":"Allowed values are missing for `Patient Name`","solution":"For Data type Checkbox/CheckboxGroup/DropDown/RadioButton/Multiselect allowed values should be configured","rowIdx":"6","column":"7"},{"id":18,"sheetLink":"13zbPhkw6Wccwa9QPvUYFKEcEvLqHk9c9KY-9EQkMqo0","sheetName":"Eva - Module Template V1.0 - CoronaGo","tab":"Data Model","type":"Warning","problem":"Allowed values are missing for `Patient HId`","solution":"For Data type Checkbox/CheckboxGroup/DropDown/RadioButton/Multiselect allowed values should be configured","rowIdx":"8","column":"7"},{"id":19,"sheetLink":"13zbPhkw6Wccwa9QPvUYFKEcEvLqHk9c9KY-9EQkMqo0","sheetName":"Eva - Module Template V1.0 - CoronaGo","tab":"List Pages","type":"Warning","problem":"Column field `Date of Birth` not found in datamodel","solution":"Configure value for the column in list page","rowIdx":"4","column":"6"},{"id":20,"sheetLink":"13zbPhkw6Wccwa9QPvUYFKEcEvLqHk9c9KY-9EQkMqo0","sheetName":"Eva - Module Template V1.0 - CoronaGo","tab":"List Pages","type":"Warning","problem":"Column field `Date of Birth` not found in datamodel","solution":"Configure value for the column in list page","rowIdx":"4","column":"6"},{"id":21,"sheetLink":"13zbPhkw6Wccwa9QPvUYFKEcEvLqHk9c9KY-9EQkMqo0","sheetName":"Eva - Module Template V1.0 - CoronaGo","tab":"List Pages","type":"Warning","problem":"Column field `Date of Birth` not found in datamodel","solution":"Configure value for the column in list page","rowIdx":"5","column":"6"},{"id":22,"sheetLink":"13zbPhkw6Wccwa9QPvUYFKEcEvLqHk9c9KY-9EQkMqo0","sheetName":"Eva - Module Template V1.0 - CoronaGo","tab":"List Pages","type":"Warning","problem":"Column field `Date of Birth` not found in datamodel","solution":"Configure value for the column in list page","rowIdx":"5","column":"6"},{"id":23,"sheetLink":"13zbPhkw6Wccwa9QPvUYFKEcEvLqHk9c9KY-9EQkMqo0","sheetName":"Eva - Module Template V1.0 - CoronaGo","tab":"List Pages","type":"Warning","problem":"Column field `Date of Birth` not found in datamodel","solution":"Configure value for the column in list page","rowIdx":"6","column":"6"},{"id":24,"sheetLink":"13zbPhkw6Wccwa9QPvUYFKEcEvLqHk9c9KY-9EQkMqo0","sheetName":"Eva - Module Template V1.0 - CoronaGo","tab":"List Pages","type":"Warning","problem":"Column field `Date of Birth` not found in datamodel","solution":"Configure value for the column in list page","rowIdx":"6","column":"6"},{"id":25,"sheetLink":"13zbPhkw6Wccwa9QPvUYFKEcEvLqHk9c9KY-9EQkMqo0","sheetName":"Eva - Module Template V1.0 - CoronaGo","tab":"List Pages","type":"Warning","problem":"Column field `Date of Birth` not found in datamodel","solution":"Configure value for the column in list page","rowIdx":"7","column":"6"},{"id":26,"sheetLink":"13zbPhkw6Wccwa9QPvUYFKEcEvLqHk9c9KY-9EQkMqo0","sheetName":"Eva - Module Template V1.0 - CoronaGo","tab":"List Pages","type":"Warning","problem":"Column field `Date of Birth` not found in datamodel","solution":"Configure value for the column in list page","rowIdx":"7","column":"6"},{"id":27,"sheetLink":"13zbPhkw6Wccwa9QPvUYFKEcEvLqHk9c9KY-9EQkMqo0","sheetName":"Eva - Module Template V1.0 - CoronaGo","tab":"List Pages","type":"Warning","problem":"Column field `Date of Birth` not found in datamodel","solution":"Configure value for the column in list page","rowIdx":"8","column":"6"},{"id":28,"sheetLink":"13zbPhkw6Wccwa9QPvUYFKEcEvLqHk9c9KY-9EQkMqo0","sheetName":"Eva - Module Template V1.0 - CoronaGo","tab":"List Pages","type":"Warning","problem":"Column field `Date of Birth` not found in datamodel","solution":"Configure value for the column in list page","rowIdx":"8","column":"6"},{"id":29,"sheetLink":"13zbPhkw6Wccwa9QPvUYFKEcEvLqHk9c9KY-9EQkMqo0","sheetName":"Eva - Module Template V1.0 - CoronaGo","tab":"Data Model","type":"Warning","problem":"Allowed values are missing for `Hospital Name`","solution":"For Data type Checkbox/CheckboxGroup/DropDown/RadioButton/Multiselect allowed values should be configured","rowIdx":"45","column":"7"},{"id":30,"sheetLink":"13zbPhkw6Wccwa9QPvUYFKEcEvLqHk9c9KY-9EQkMqo0","sheetName":"Eva - Module Template V1.0 - CoronaGo","tab":"Data Model","type":"Warning","problem":"Allowed values are missing for `Item`","solution":"For Data type Checkbox/CheckboxGroup/DropDown/RadioButton/Multiselect allowed values should be configured","rowIdx":"46","column":"7"},{"id":31,"sheetLink":"13zbPhkw6Wccwa9QPvUYFKEcEvLqHk9c9KY-9EQkMqo0","sheetName":"Eva - Module Template V1.0 - CoronaGo","tab":"Data Model","type":"Warning","problem":"Allowed values are missing for `Item`","solution":"For Data type Checkbox/CheckboxGroup/DropDown/RadioButton/Multiselect allowed values should be configured","rowIdx":"49","column":"7"},{"id":32,"sheetLink":"13zbPhkw6Wccwa9QPvUYFKEcEvLqHk9c9KY-9EQkMqo0","sheetName":"Eva - Module Template V1.0 - CoronaGo","tab":"Data Model","type":"Warning","problem":"Allowed values are missing for `Patient Hid`","solution":"For Data type Checkbox/CheckboxGroup/DropDown/RadioButton/Multiselect allowed values should be configured","rowIdx":"24","column":"7"},{"id":33,"sheetLink":"13zbPhkw6Wccwa9QPvUYFKEcEvLqHk9c9KY-9EQkMqo0","sheetName":"Eva - Module Template V1.0 - CoronaGo","tab":"Data Model","type":"Warning","problem":"Allowed values are missing for `Patient Name`","solution":"For Data type Checkbox/CheckboxGroup/DropDown/RadioButton/Multiselect allowed values should be configured","rowIdx":"25","column":"7"},{"id":34,"sheetLink":"13zbPhkw6Wccwa9QPvUYFKEcEvLqHk9c9KY-9EQkMqo0","sheetName":"Eva - Module Template V1.0 - CoronaGo","tab":"Data Model","type":"Warning","problem":"Allowed values are missing for `Meeting Id`","solution":"For Data type Checkbox/CheckboxGroup/DropDown/RadioButton/Multiselect allowed values should be configured","rowIdx":"27","column":"7"},{"id":35,"sheetLink":"13zbPhkw6Wccwa9QPvUYFKEcEvLqHk9c9KY-9EQkMqo0","sheetName":"Eva - Module Template V1.0 - CoronaGo","tab":"Data Model","type":"Warning","problem":"Allowed values are missing for `Doctor Id`","solution":"For Data type Checkbox/CheckboxGroup/DropDown/RadioButton/Multiselect allowed values should be configured","rowIdx":"28","column":"7"},{"id":36,"sheetLink":"13zbPhkw6Wccwa9QPvUYFKEcEvLqHk9c9KY-9EQkMqo0","sheetName":"Eva - Module Template V1.0 - CoronaGo","tab":"Data Model","type":"Warning","problem":"Allowed values are missing for `Doctor Name`","solution":"For Data type Checkbox/CheckboxGroup/DropDown/RadioButton/Multiselect allowed values should be configured","rowIdx":"29","column":"7"},{"id":37,"sheetLink":"13zbPhkw6Wccwa9QPvUYFKEcEvLqHk9c9KY-9EQkMqo0","sheetName":"Eva - Module Template V1.0 - CoronaGo","tab":"Data Model","type":"Warning","problem":"Allowed values are missing for `Meeting Status`","solution":"For Data type Checkbox/CheckboxGroup/DropDown/RadioButton/Multiselect allowed values should be configured","rowIdx":"33","column":"7"},{"id":38,"sheetLink":"13zbPhkw6Wccwa9QPvUYFKEcEvLqHk9c9KY-9EQkMqo0","sheetName":"Eva - Module Template V1.0 - CoronaGo","tab":"Data Model","type":"Warning","problem":"Allowed values are missing for `Meeting Url`","solution":"For Data type Checkbox/CheckboxGroup/DropDown/RadioButton/Multiselect allowed values should be configured","rowIdx":"34","column":"7"},{"id":39,"sheetLink":"13zbPhkw6Wccwa9QPvUYFKEcEvLqHk9c9KY-9EQkMqo0","sheetName":"Eva - Module Template V1.0 - CoronaGo","tab":"Data Model","type":"Warning","problem":"Allowed values are missing for `Doctor Name`","solution":"For Data type Checkbox/CheckboxGroup/DropDown/RadioButton/Multiselect allowed values should be configured","rowIdx":"38","column":"7"},{"id":40,"sheetLink":"13zbPhkw6Wccwa9QPvUYFKEcEvLqHk9c9KY-9EQkMqo0","sheetName":"Eva - Module Template V1.0 - CoronaGo","tab":"Data Model","type":"Warning","problem":"Allowed values are missing for `Item`","solution":"For Data type Checkbox/CheckboxGroup/DropDown/RadioButton/Multiselect allowed values should be configured","rowIdx":"42","column":"7"},{"id":41,"sheetLink":"13zbPhkw6Wccwa9QPvUYFKEcEvLqHk9c9KY-9EQkMqo0","sheetName":"Eva - Module Template V1.0 - CoronaGo","tab":"Data Model","type":"Warning","problem":"Allowed values are missing for `Patient Name`","solution":"For Data type Checkbox/CheckboxGroup/DropDown/RadioButton/Multiselect allowed values should be configured","rowIdx":"60","column":"7"},{"id":42,"sheetLink":"13zbPhkw6Wccwa9QPvUYFKEcEvLqHk9c9KY-9EQkMqo0","sheetName":"Eva - Module Template V1.0 - CoronaGo","tab":"Data Model","type":"Warning","problem":"Allowed values are missing for `Patient HId`","solution":"For Data type Checkbox/CheckboxGroup/DropDown/RadioButton/Multiselect allowed values should be configured","rowIdx":"62","column":"7"},{"id":43,"sheetLink":"13zbPhkw6Wccwa9QPvUYFKEcEvLqHk9c9KY-9EQkMqo0","sheetName":"Eva - Module Template V1.0 - CoronaGo","tab":"Data Model","type":"Warning","problem":"Allowed values are missing for `City`","solution":"For Data type Checkbox/CheckboxGroup/DropDown/RadioButton/Multiselect allowed values should be configured","rowIdx":"67","column":"7"},{"id":44,"sheetLink":"13zbPhkw6Wccwa9QPvUYFKEcEvLqHk9c9KY-9EQkMqo0","sheetName":"Eva - Module Template V1.0 - CoronaGo","tab":"Data Model","type":"Warning","problem":"Allowed values are missing for `Insurance Provider`","solution":"For Data type Checkbox/CheckboxGroup/DropDown/RadioButton/Multiselect allowed values should be configured","rowIdx":"69","column":"7"},{"id":45,"sheetLink":"13zbPhkw6Wccwa9QPvUYFKEcEvLqHk9c9KY-9EQkMqo0","sheetName":"Eva - Module Template V1.0 - CoronaGo","tab":"Data Model","type":"Warning","problem":"Allowed values are missing for `Patient Name`","solution":"For Data type Checkbox/CheckboxGroup/DropDown/RadioButton/Multiselect allowed values should be configured","rowIdx":"6","column":"7"},{"id":46,"sheetLink":"13zbPhkw6Wccwa9QPvUYFKEcEvLqHk9c9KY-9EQkMqo0","sheetName":"Eva - Module Template V1.0 - CoronaGo","tab":"Data Model","type":"Warning","problem":"Allowed values are missing for `Patient HId`","solution":"For Data type Checkbox/CheckboxGroup/DropDown/RadioButton/Multiselect allowed values should be configured","rowIdx":"8","column":"7"},{"id":47,"sheetLink":"13zbPhkw6Wccwa9QPvUYFKEcEvLqHk9c9KY-9EQkMqo0","sheetName":"Eva - Module Template V1.0 - CoronaGo","tab":"List Pages","type":"Warning","problem":"Column field `Date of Birth` not found in datamodel","solution":"Configure value for the column in list page","rowIdx":"4","column":"6"},{"id":48,"sheetLink":"13zbPhkw6Wccwa9QPvUYFKEcEvLqHk9c9KY-9EQkMqo0","sheetName":"Eva - Module Template V1.0 - CoronaGo","tab":"List Pages","type":"Warning","problem":"Column field `Date of Birth` not found in datamodel","solution":"Configure value for the column in list page","rowIdx":"4","column":"6"},{"id":49,"sheetLink":"13zbPhkw6Wccwa9QPvUYFKEcEvLqHk9c9KY-9EQkMqo0","sheetName":"Eva - Module Template V1.0 - CoronaGo","tab":"List Pages","type":"Warning","problem":"Column field `Date of Birth` not found in datamodel","solution":"Configure value for the column in list page","rowIdx":"5","column":"6"},{"id":50,"sheetLink":"13zbPhkw6Wccwa9QPvUYFKEcEvLqHk9c9KY-9EQkMqo0","sheetName":"Eva - Module Template V1.0 - CoronaGo","tab":"List Pages","type":"Warning","problem":"Column field `Date of Birth` not found in datamodel","solution":"Configure value for the column in list page","rowIdx":"5","column":"6"},{"id":51,"sheetLink":"13zbPhkw6Wccwa9QPvUYFKEcEvLqHk9c9KY-9EQkMqo0","sheetName":"Eva - Module Template V1.0 - CoronaGo","tab":"List Pages","type":"Warning","problem":"Column field `Date of Birth` not found in datamodel","solution":"Configure value for the column in list page","rowIdx":"6","column":"6"},{"id":52,"sheetLink":"13zbPhkw6Wccwa9QPvUYFKEcEvLqHk9c9KY-9EQkMqo0","sheetName":"Eva - Module Template V1.0 - CoronaGo","tab":"List Pages","type":"Warning","problem":"Column field `Date of Birth` not found in datamodel","solution":"Configure value for the column in list page","rowIdx":"6","column":"6"},{"id":53,"sheetLink":"13zbPhkw6Wccwa9QPvUYFKEcEvLqHk9c9KY-9EQkMqo0","sheetName":"Eva - Module Template V1.0 - CoronaGo","tab":"List Pages","type":"Warning","problem":"Column field `Date of Birth` not found in datamodel","solution":"Configure value for the column in list page","rowIdx":"7","column":"6"},{"id":54,"sheetLink":"13zbPhkw6Wccwa9QPvUYFKEcEvLqHk9c9KY-9EQkMqo0","sheetName":"Eva - Module Template V1.0 - CoronaGo","tab":"List Pages","type":"Warning","problem":"Column field `Date of Birth` not found in datamodel","solution":"Configure value for the column in list page","rowIdx":"7","column":"6"},{"id":55,"sheetLink":"13zbPhkw6Wccwa9QPvUYFKEcEvLqHk9c9KY-9EQkMqo0","sheetName":"Eva - Module Template V1.0 - CoronaGo","tab":"List Pages","type":"Warning","problem":"Column field `Date of Birth` not found in datamodel","solution":"Configure value for the column in list page","rowIdx":"8","column":"6"},{"id":56,"sheetLink":"13zbPhkw6Wccwa9QPvUYFKEcEvLqHk9c9KY-9EQkMqo0","sheetName":"Eva - Module Template V1.0 - CoronaGo","tab":"List Pages","type":"Warning","problem":"Column field `Date of Birth` not found in datamodel","solution":"Configure value for the column in list page","rowIdx":"8","column":"6"}]},{"id":4,"action":"Detail Page Generation","dateTime":1585118441459,"items":[{"id":1,"sheetLink":"13zbPhkw6Wccwa9QPvUYFKEcEvLqHk9c9KY-9EQkMqo0","sheetName":"Eva - Module Template V1.0 - CoronaGo","tab":"Data Model","type":"Warning","problem":"Allowed values are missing for `Hospital Name`","solution":"For Data type Checkbox/CheckboxGroup/DropDown/RadioButton/Multiselect allowed values should be configured","rowIdx":"59","column":"7"},{"id":2,"sheetLink":"13zbPhkw6Wccwa9QPvUYFKEcEvLqHk9c9KY-9EQkMqo0","sheetName":"Eva - Module Template V1.0 - CoronaGo","tab":"Data Model","type":"Warning","problem":"Allowed values are missing for `Item`","solution":"For Data type Checkbox/CheckboxGroup/DropDown/RadioButton/Multiselect allowed values should be configured","rowIdx":"60","column":"7"},{"id":3,"sheetLink":"13zbPhkw6Wccwa9QPvUYFKEcEvLqHk9c9KY-9EQkMqo0","sheetName":"Eva - Module Template V1.0 - CoronaGo","tab":"Data Model","type":"Warning","problem":"Allowed values are missing for `Item`","solution":"For Data type Checkbox/CheckboxGroup/DropDown/RadioButton/Multiselect allowed values should be configured","rowIdx":"63","column":"7"},{"id":4,"sheetLink":"13zbPhkw6Wccwa9QPvUYFKEcEvLqHk9c9KY-9EQkMqo0","sheetName":"Eva - Module Template V1.0 - CoronaGo","tab":"Data Model","type":"Warning","problem":"Allowed values are missing for `Patient Hid`","solution":"For Data type Checkbox/CheckboxGroup/DropDown/RadioButton/Multiselect allowed values should be configured","rowIdx":"38","column":"7"},{"id":5,"sheetLink":"13zbPhkw6Wccwa9QPvUYFKEcEvLqHk9c9KY-9EQkMqo0","sheetName":"Eva - Module Template V1.0 - CoronaGo","tab":"Data Model","type":"Warning","problem":"Allowed values are missing for `Patient Name`","solution":"For Data type Checkbox/CheckboxGroup/DropDown/RadioButton/Multiselect allowed values should be configured","rowIdx":"39","column":"7"},{"id":6,"sheetLink":"13zbPhkw6Wccwa9QPvUYFKEcEvLqHk9c9KY-9EQkMqo0","sheetName":"Eva - Module Template V1.0 - CoronaGo","tab":"Data Model","type":"Warning","problem":"Allowed values are missing for `Meeting Id`","solution":"For Data type Checkbox/CheckboxGroup/DropDown/RadioButton/Multiselect allowed values should be configured","rowIdx":"41","column":"7"},{"id":7,"sheetLink":"13zbPhkw6Wccwa9QPvUYFKEcEvLqHk9c9KY-9EQkMqo0","sheetName":"Eva - Module Template V1.0 - CoronaGo","tab":"Data Model","type":"Warning","problem":"Allowed values are missing for `Doctor Id`","solution":"For Data type Checkbox/CheckboxGroup/DropDown/RadioButton/Multiselect allowed values should be configured","rowIdx":"42","column":"7"},{"id":8,"sheetLink":"13zbPhkw6Wccwa9QPvUYFKEcEvLqHk9c9KY-9EQkMqo0","sheetName":"Eva - Module Template V1.0 - CoronaGo","tab":"Data Model","type":"Warning","problem":"Allowed values are missing for `Doctor Name`","solution":"For Data type Checkbox/CheckboxGroup/DropDown/RadioButton/Multiselect allowed values should be configured","rowIdx":"43","column":"7"},{"id":9,"sheetLink":"13zbPhkw6Wccwa9QPvUYFKEcEvLqHk9c9KY-9EQkMqo0","sheetName":"Eva - Module Template V1.0 - CoronaGo","tab":"Data Model","type":"Warning","problem":"Allowed values are missing for `Meeting Status`","solution":"For Data type Checkbox/CheckboxGroup/DropDown/RadioButton/Multiselect allowed values should be configured","rowIdx":"47","column":"7"},{"id":10,"sheetLink":"13zbPhkw6Wccwa9QPvUYFKEcEvLqHk9c9KY-9EQkMqo0","sheetName":"Eva - Module Template V1.0 - CoronaGo","tab":"Data Model","type":"Warning","problem":"Allowed values are missing for `Meeting Url`","solution":"For Data type Checkbox/CheckboxGroup/DropDown/RadioButton/Multiselect allowed values should be configured","rowIdx":"48","column":"7"},{"id":11,"sheetLink":"13zbPhkw6Wccwa9QPvUYFKEcEvLqHk9c9KY-9EQkMqo0","sheetName":"Eva - Module Template V1.0 - CoronaGo","tab":"Data Model","type":"Warning","problem":"Allowed values are missing for `Doctor Name`","solution":"For Data type Checkbox/CheckboxGroup/DropDown/RadioButton/Multiselect allowed values should be configured","rowIdx":"52","column":"7"},{"id":12,"sheetLink":"13zbPhkw6Wccwa9QPvUYFKEcEvLqHk9c9KY-9EQkMqo0","sheetName":"Eva - Module Template V1.0 - CoronaGo","tab":"Data Model","type":"Warning","problem":"Allowed values are missing for `Item`","solution":"For Data type Checkbox/CheckboxGroup/DropDown/RadioButton/Multiselect allowed values should be configured","rowIdx":"56","column":"7"},{"id":13,"sheetLink":"13zbPhkw6Wccwa9QPvUYFKEcEvLqHk9c9KY-9EQkMqo0","sheetName":"Eva - Module Template V1.0 - CoronaGo","tab":"Data Model","type":"Warning","problem":"Allowed values are missing for `Patient Name`","solution":"For Data type Checkbox/CheckboxGroup/DropDown/RadioButton/Multiselect allowed values should be configured","rowIdx":"74","column":"7"},{"id":14,"sheetLink":"13zbPhkw6Wccwa9QPvUYFKEcEvLqHk9c9KY-9EQkMqo0","sheetName":"Eva - Module Template V1.0 - CoronaGo","tab":"Data Model","type":"Warning","problem":"Allowed values are missing for `Patient HId`","solution":"For Data type Checkbox/CheckboxGroup/DropDown/RadioButton/Multiselect allowed values should be configured","rowIdx":"76","column":"7"},{"id":15,"sheetLink":"13zbPhkw6Wccwa9QPvUYFKEcEvLqHk9c9KY-9EQkMqo0","sheetName":"Eva - Module Template V1.0 - CoronaGo","tab":"Data Model","type":"Warning","problem":"Allowed values are missing for `City`","solution":"For Data type Checkbox/CheckboxGroup/DropDown/RadioButton/Multiselect allowed values should be configured","rowIdx":"81","column":"7"},{"id":16,"sheetLink":"13zbPhkw6Wccwa9QPvUYFKEcEvLqHk9c9KY-9EQkMqo0","sheetName":"Eva - Module Template V1.0 - CoronaGo","tab":"Data Model","type":"Warning","problem":"Allowed values are missing for `Insurance Provider`","solution":"For Data type Checkbox/CheckboxGroup/DropDown/RadioButton/Multiselect allowed values should be configured","rowIdx":"83","column":"7"},{"id":17,"sheetLink":"13zbPhkw6Wccwa9QPvUYFKEcEvLqHk9c9KY-9EQkMqo0","sheetName":"Eva - Module Template V1.0 - CoronaGo","tab":"Data Model","type":"Warning","problem":"Allowed values are missing for `Patient Name`","solution":"For Data type Checkbox/CheckboxGroup/DropDown/RadioButton/Multiselect allowed values should be configured","rowIdx":"6","column":"7"},{"id":18,"sheetLink":"13zbPhkw6Wccwa9QPvUYFKEcEvLqHk9c9KY-9EQkMqo0","sheetName":"Eva - Module Template V1.0 - CoronaGo","tab":"Data Model","type":"Warning","problem":"Allowed values are missing for `Patient HId`","solution":"For Data type Checkbox/CheckboxGroup/DropDown/RadioButton/Multiselect allowed values should be configured","rowIdx":"8","column":"7"},{"id":19,"sheetLink":"13zbPhkw6Wccwa9QPvUYFKEcEvLqHk9c9KY-9EQkMqo0","sheetName":"Eva - Module Template V1.0 - CoronaGo","tab":"List Pages","type":"Warning","problem":"Column field `Date of Birth` not found in datamodel","solution":"Configure value for the column in list page","rowIdx":"4","column":"6"},{"id":20,"sheetLink":"13zbPhkw6Wccwa9QPvUYFKEcEvLqHk9c9KY-9EQkMqo0","sheetName":"Eva - Module Template V1.0 - CoronaGo","tab":"List Pages","type":"Warning","problem":"Column field `Date of Birth` not found in datamodel","solution":"Configure value for the column in list page","rowIdx":"4","column":"6"},{"id":21,"sheetLink":"13zbPhkw6Wccwa9QPvUYFKEcEvLqHk9c9KY-9EQkMqo0","sheetName":"Eva - Module Template V1.0 - CoronaGo","tab":"List Pages","type":"Warning","problem":"Column field `Date of Birth` not found in datamodel","solution":"Configure value for the column in list page","rowIdx":"5","column":"6"},{"id":22,"sheetLink":"13zbPhkw6Wccwa9QPvUYFKEcEvLqHk9c9KY-9EQkMqo0","sheetName":"Eva - Module Template V1.0 - CoronaGo","tab":"List Pages","type":"Warning","problem":"Column field `Date of Birth` not found in datamodel","solution":"Configure value for the column in list page","rowIdx":"5","column":"6"},{"id":23,"sheetLink":"13zbPhkw6Wccwa9QPvUYFKEcEvLqHk9c9KY-9EQkMqo0","sheetName":"Eva - Module Template V1.0 - CoronaGo","tab":"List Pages","type":"Warning","problem":"Column field `Date of Birth` not found in datamodel","solution":"Configure value for the column in list page","rowIdx":"6","column":"6"},{"id":24,"sheetLink":"13zbPhkw6Wccwa9QPvUYFKEcEvLqHk9c9KY-9EQkMqo0","sheetName":"Eva - Module Template V1.0 - CoronaGo","tab":"List Pages","type":"Warning","problem":"Column field `Date of Birth` not found in datamodel","solution":"Configure value for the column in list page","rowIdx":"6","column":"6"},{"id":25,"sheetLink":"13zbPhkw6Wccwa9QPvUYFKEcEvLqHk9c9KY-9EQkMqo0","sheetName":"Eva - Module Template V1.0 - CoronaGo","tab":"List Pages","type":"Warning","problem":"Column field `Date of Birth` not found in datamodel","solution":"Configure value for the column in list page","rowIdx":"7","column":"6"},{"id":26,"sheetLink":"13zbPhkw6Wccwa9QPvUYFKEcEvLqHk9c9KY-9EQkMqo0","sheetName":"Eva - Module Template V1.0 - CoronaGo","tab":"List Pages","type":"Warning","problem":"Column field `Date of Birth` not found in datamodel","solution":"Configure value for the column in list page","rowIdx":"7","column":"6"},{"id":27,"sheetLink":"13zbPhkw6Wccwa9QPvUYFKEcEvLqHk9c9KY-9EQkMqo0","sheetName":"Eva - Module Template V1.0 - CoronaGo","tab":"List Pages","type":"Warning","problem":"Column field `Date of Birth` not found in datamodel","solution":"Configure value for the column in list page","rowIdx":"8","column":"6"},{"id":28,"sheetLink":"13zbPhkw6Wccwa9QPvUYFKEcEvLqHk9c9KY-9EQkMqo0","sheetName":"Eva - Module Template V1.0 - CoronaGo","tab":"List Pages","type":"Warning","problem":"Column field `Date of Birth` not found in datamodel","solution":"Configure value for the column in list page","rowIdx":"8","column":"6"}]},{"id":5,"action":"List Page Generation","dateTime":1585118396522,"items":[{"id":1,"sheetLink":"13zbPhkw6Wccwa9QPvUYFKEcEvLqHk9c9KY-9EQkMqo0","sheetName":"Eva - Module Template V1.0 - CoronaGo","tab":"Data Model","type":"Warning","problem":"Allowed values are missing for `Hospital Name`","solution":"For Data type Checkbox/CheckboxGroup/DropDown/RadioButton/Multiselect allowed values should be configured","rowIdx":"59","column":"7"},{"id":2,"sheetLink":"13zbPhkw6Wccwa9QPvUYFKEcEvLqHk9c9KY-9EQkMqo0","sheetName":"Eva - Module Template V1.0 - CoronaGo","tab":"Data Model","type":"Warning","problem":"Allowed values are missing for `Item`","solution":"For Data type Checkbox/CheckboxGroup/DropDown/RadioButton/Multiselect allowed values should be configured","rowIdx":"60","column":"7"},{"id":3,"sheetLink":"13zbPhkw6Wccwa9QPvUYFKEcEvLqHk9c9KY-9EQkMqo0","sheetName":"Eva - Module Template V1.0 - CoronaGo","tab":"Data Model","type":"Warning","problem":"Allowed values are missing for `Item`","solution":"For Data type Checkbox/CheckboxGroup/DropDown/RadioButton/Multiselect allowed values should be configured","rowIdx":"63","column":"7"},{"id":4,"sheetLink":"13zbPhkw6Wccwa9QPvUYFKEcEvLqHk9c9KY-9EQkMqo0","sheetName":"Eva - Module Template V1.0 - CoronaGo","tab":"Data Model","type":"Warning","problem":"Allowed values are missing for `Patient Hid`","solution":"For Data type Checkbox/CheckboxGroup/DropDown/RadioButton/Multiselect allowed values should be configured","rowIdx":"38","column":"7"},{"id":5,"sheetLink":"13zbPhkw6Wccwa9QPvUYFKEcEvLqHk9c9KY-9EQkMqo0","sheetName":"Eva - Module Template V1.0 - CoronaGo","tab":"Data Model","type":"Warning","problem":"Allowed values are missing for `Patient Name`","solution":"For Data type Checkbox/CheckboxGroup/DropDown/RadioButton/Multiselect allowed values should be configured","rowIdx":"39","column":"7"},{"id":6,"sheetLink":"13zbPhkw6Wccwa9QPvUYFKEcEvLqHk9c9KY-9EQkMqo0","sheetName":"Eva - Module Template V1.0 - CoronaGo","tab":"Data Model","type":"Warning","problem":"Allowed values are missing for `Meeting Id`","solution":"For Data type Checkbox/CheckboxGroup/DropDown/RadioButton/Multiselect allowed values should be configured","rowIdx":"41","column":"7"},{"id":7,"sheetLink":"13zbPhkw6Wccwa9QPvUYFKEcEvLqHk9c9KY-9EQkMqo0","sheetName":"Eva - Module Template V1.0 - CoronaGo","tab":"Data Model","type":"Warning","problem":"Allowed values are missing for `Doctor Id`","solution":"For Data type Checkbox/CheckboxGroup/DropDown/RadioButton/Multiselect allowed values should be configured","rowIdx":"42","column":"7"},{"id":8,"sheetLink":"13zbPhkw6Wccwa9QPvUYFKEcEvLqHk9c9KY-9EQkMqo0","sheetName":"Eva - Module Template V1.0 - CoronaGo","tab":"Data Model","type":"Warning","problem":"Allowed values are missing for `Doctor Name`","solution":"For Data type Checkbox/CheckboxGroup/DropDown/RadioButton/Multiselect allowed values should be configured","rowIdx":"43","column":"7"},{"id":9,"sheetLink":"13zbPhkw6Wccwa9QPvUYFKEcEvLqHk9c9KY-9EQkMqo0","sheetName":"Eva - Module Template V1.0 - CoronaGo","tab":"Data Model","type":"Warning","problem":"Allowed values are missing for `Meeting Status`","solution":"For Data type Checkbox/CheckboxGroup/DropDown/RadioButton/Multiselect allowed values should be configured","rowIdx":"47","column":"7"},{"id":10,"sheetLink":"13zbPhkw6Wccwa9QPvUYFKEcEvLqHk9c9KY-9EQkMqo0","sheetName":"Eva - Module Template V1.0 - CoronaGo","tab":"Data Model","type":"Warning","problem":"Allowed values are missing for `Meeting Url`","solution":"For Data type Checkbox/CheckboxGroup/DropDown/RadioButton/Multiselect allowed values should be configured","rowIdx":"48","column":"7"},{"id":11,"sheetLink":"13zbPhkw6Wccwa9QPvUYFKEcEvLqHk9c9KY-9EQkMqo0","sheetName":"Eva - Module Template V1.0 - CoronaGo","tab":"Data Model","type":"Warning","problem":"Allowed values are missing for `Doctor Name`","solution":"For Data type Checkbox/CheckboxGroup/DropDown/RadioButton/Multiselect allowed values should be configured","rowIdx":"52","column":"7"},{"id":12,"sheetLink":"13zbPhkw6Wccwa9QPvUYFKEcEvLqHk9c9KY-9EQkMqo0","sheetName":"Eva - Module Template V1.0 - CoronaGo","tab":"Data Model","type":"Warning","problem":"Allowed values are missing for `Item`","solution":"For Data type Checkbox/CheckboxGroup/DropDown/RadioButton/Multiselect allowed values should be configured","rowIdx":"56","column":"7"},{"id":13,"sheetLink":"13zbPhkw6Wccwa9QPvUYFKEcEvLqHk9c9KY-9EQkMqo0","sheetName":"Eva - Module Template V1.0 - CoronaGo","tab":"Data Model","type":"Warning","problem":"Allowed values are missing for `Patient Name`","solution":"For Data type Checkbox/CheckboxGroup/DropDown/RadioButton/Multiselect allowed values should be configured","rowIdx":"74","column":"7"},{"id":14,"sheetLink":"13zbPhkw6Wccwa9QPvUYFKEcEvLqHk9c9KY-9EQkMqo0","sheetName":"Eva - Module Template V1.0 - CoronaGo","tab":"Data Model","type":"Warning","problem":"Allowed values are missing for `Patient HId`","solution":"For Data type Checkbox/CheckboxGroup/DropDown/RadioButton/Multiselect allowed values should be configured","rowIdx":"76","column":"7"},{"id":15,"sheetLink":"13zbPhkw6Wccwa9QPvUYFKEcEvLqHk9c9KY-9EQkMqo0","sheetName":"Eva - Module Template V1.0 - CoronaGo","tab":"Data Model","type":"Warning","problem":"Allowed values are missing for `City`","solution":"For Data type Checkbox/CheckboxGroup/DropDown/RadioButton/Multiselect allowed values should be configured","rowIdx":"81","column":"7"},{"id":16,"sheetLink":"13zbPhkw6Wccwa9QPvUYFKEcEvLqHk9c9KY-9EQkMqo0","sheetName":"Eva - Module Template V1.0 - CoronaGo","tab":"Data Model","type":"Warning","problem":"Allowed values are missing for `Insurance Provider`","solution":"For Data type Checkbox/CheckboxGroup/DropDown/RadioButton/Multiselect allowed values should be configured","rowIdx":"83","column":"7"},{"id":17,"sheetLink":"13zbPhkw6Wccwa9QPvUYFKEcEvLqHk9c9KY-9EQkMqo0","sheetName":"Eva - Module Template V1.0 - CoronaGo","tab":"Data Model","type":"Warning","problem":"Allowed values are missing for `Patient Name`","solution":"For Data type Checkbox/CheckboxGroup/DropDown/RadioButton/Multiselect allowed values should be configured","rowIdx":"6","column":"7"},{"id":18,"sheetLink":"13zbPhkw6Wccwa9QPvUYFKEcEvLqHk9c9KY-9EQkMqo0","sheetName":"Eva - Module Template V1.0 - CoronaGo","tab":"Data Model","type":"Warning","problem":"Allowed values are missing for `Patient HId`","solution":"For Data type Checkbox/CheckboxGroup/DropDown/RadioButton/Multiselect allowed values should be configured","rowIdx":"8","column":"7"},{"id":19,"sheetLink":"13zbPhkw6Wccwa9QPvUYFKEcEvLqHk9c9KY-9EQkMqo0","sheetName":"Eva - Module Template V1.0 - CoronaGo","tab":"List Pages","type":"Warning","problem":"Column field `Date of Birth` not found in datamodel","solution":"Configure value for the column in list page","rowIdx":"4","column":"6"},{"id":20,"sheetLink":"13zbPhkw6Wccwa9QPvUYFKEcEvLqHk9c9KY-9EQkMqo0","sheetName":"Eva - Module Template V1.0 - CoronaGo","tab":"List Pages","type":"Warning","problem":"Column field `Date of Birth` not found in datamodel","solution":"Configure value for the column in list page","rowIdx":"4","column":"6"},{"id":21,"sheetLink":"13zbPhkw6Wccwa9QPvUYFKEcEvLqHk9c9KY-9EQkMqo0","sheetName":"Eva - Module Template V1.0 - CoronaGo","tab":"List Pages","type":"Warning","problem":"Column field `Date of Birth` not found in datamodel","solution":"Configure value for the column in list page","rowIdx":"5","column":"6"},{"id":22,"sheetLink":"13zbPhkw6Wccwa9QPvUYFKEcEvLqHk9c9KY-9EQkMqo0","sheetName":"Eva - Module Template V1.0 - CoronaGo","tab":"List Pages","type":"Warning","problem":"Column field `Date of Birth` not found in datamodel","solution":"Configure value for the column in list page","rowIdx":"5","column":"6"},{"id":23,"sheetLink":"13zbPhkw6Wccwa9QPvUYFKEcEvLqHk9c9KY-9EQkMqo0","sheetName":"Eva - Module Template V1.0 - CoronaGo","tab":"List Pages","type":"Warning","problem":"Column field `Date of Birth` not found in datamodel","solution":"Configure value for the column in list page","rowIdx":"6","column":"6"},{"id":24,"sheetLink":"13zbPhkw6Wccwa9QPvUYFKEcEvLqHk9c9KY-9EQkMqo0","sheetName":"Eva - Module Template V1.0 - CoronaGo","tab":"List Pages","type":"Warning","problem":"Column field `Date of Birth` not found in datamodel","solution":"Configure value for the column in list page","rowIdx":"6","column":"6"},{"id":25,"sheetLink":"13zbPhkw6Wccwa9QPvUYFKEcEvLqHk9c9KY-9EQkMqo0","sheetName":"Eva - Module Template V1.0 - CoronaGo","tab":"List Pages","type":"Warning","problem":"Column field `Date of Birth` not found in datamodel","solution":"Configure value for the column in list page","rowIdx":"7","column":"6"},{"id":26,"sheetLink":"13zbPhkw6Wccwa9QPvUYFKEcEvLqHk9c9KY-9EQkMqo0","sheetName":"Eva - Module Template V1.0 - CoronaGo","tab":"List Pages","type":"Warning","problem":"Column field `Date of Birth` not found in datamodel","solution":"Configure value for the column in list page","rowIdx":"7","column":"6"},{"id":27,"sheetLink":"13zbPhkw6Wccwa9QPvUYFKEcEvLqHk9c9KY-9EQkMqo0","sheetName":"Eva - Module Template V1.0 - CoronaGo","tab":"List Pages","type":"Warning","problem":"Column field `Date of Birth` not found in datamodel","solution":"Configure value for the column in list page","rowIdx":"8","column":"6"},{"id":28,"sheetLink":"13zbPhkw6Wccwa9QPvUYFKEcEvLqHk9c9KY-9EQkMqo0","sheetName":"Eva - Module Template V1.0 - CoronaGo","tab":"List Pages","type":"Warning","problem":"Column field `Date of Birth` not found in datamodel","solution":"Configure value for the column in list page","rowIdx":"8","column":"6"}]},{"id":6,"action":"Detail Page Generation","dateTime":1585117998492,"items":[{"id":1,"sheetLink":"13zbPhkw6Wccwa9QPvUYFKEcEvLqHk9c9KY-9EQkMqo0","sheetName":"Eva - Module Template V1.0 - CoronaGo","tab":"Data Model","type":"Warning","problem":"Allowed values are missing for `Hospital Name`","solution":"For Data type Checkbox/CheckboxGroup/DropDown/RadioButton/Multiselect allowed values should be configured","rowIdx":"59","column":"7"},{"id":2,"sheetLink":"13zbPhkw6Wccwa9QPvUYFKEcEvLqHk9c9KY-9EQkMqo0","sheetName":"Eva - Module Template V1.0 - CoronaGo","tab":"Data Model","type":"Warning","problem":"Allowed values are missing for `Item`","solution":"For Data type Checkbox/CheckboxGroup/DropDown/RadioButton/Multiselect allowed values should be configured","rowIdx":"60","column":"7"},{"id":3,"sheetLink":"13zbPhkw6Wccwa9QPvUYFKEcEvLqHk9c9KY-9EQkMqo0","sheetName":"Eva - Module Template V1.0 - CoronaGo","tab":"Data Model","type":"Warning","problem":"Allowed values are missing for `Item`","solution":"For Data type Checkbox/CheckboxGroup/DropDown/RadioButton/Multiselect allowed values should be configured","rowIdx":"63","column":"7"},{"id":4,"sheetLink":"13zbPhkw6Wccwa9QPvUYFKEcEvLqHk9c9KY-9EQkMqo0","sheetName":"Eva - Module Template V1.0 - CoronaGo","tab":"Data Model","type":"Warning","problem":"Allowed values are missing for `Patient Hid`","solution":"For Data type Checkbox/CheckboxGroup/DropDown/RadioButton/Multiselect allowed values should be configured","rowIdx":"38","column":"7"},{"id":5,"sheetLink":"13zbPhkw6Wccwa9QPvUYFKEcEvLqHk9c9KY-9EQkMqo0","sheetName":"Eva - Module Template V1.0 - CoronaGo","tab":"Data Model","type":"Warning","problem":"Allowed values are missing for `Patient Name`","solution":"For Data type Checkbox/CheckboxGroup/DropDown/RadioButton/Multiselect allowed values should be configured","rowIdx":"39","column":"7"},{"id":6,"sheetLink":"13zbPhkw6Wccwa9QPvUYFKEcEvLqHk9c9KY-9EQkMqo0","sheetName":"Eva - Module Template V1.0 - CoronaGo","tab":"Data Model","type":"Warning","problem":"Allowed values are missing for `Meeting Id`","solution":"For Data type Checkbox/CheckboxGroup/DropDown/RadioButton/Multiselect allowed values should be configured","rowIdx":"41","column":"7"},{"id":7,"sheetLink":"13zbPhkw6Wccwa9QPvUYFKEcEvLqHk9c9KY-9EQkMqo0","sheetName":"Eva - Module Template V1.0 - CoronaGo","tab":"Data Model","type":"Warning","problem":"Allowed values are missing for `Doctor Id`","solution":"For Data type Checkbox/CheckboxGroup/DropDown/RadioButton/Multiselect allowed values should be configured","rowIdx":"42","column":"7"},{"id":8,"sheetLink":"13zbPhkw6Wccwa9QPvUYFKEcEvLqHk9c9KY-9EQkMqo0","sheetName":"Eva - Module Template V1.0 - CoronaGo","tab":"Data Model","type":"Warning","problem":"Allowed values are missing for `Doctor Name`","solution":"For Data type Checkbox/CheckboxGroup/DropDown/RadioButton/Multiselect allowed values should be configured","rowIdx":"43","column":"7"},{"id":9,"sheetLink":"13zbPhkw6Wccwa9QPvUYFKEcEvLqHk9c9KY-9EQkMqo0","sheetName":"Eva - Module Template V1.0 - CoronaGo","tab":"Data Model","type":"Warning","problem":"Allowed values are missing for `Meeting Status`","solution":"For Data type Checkbox/CheckboxGroup/DropDown/RadioButton/Multiselect allowed values should be configured","rowIdx":"47","column":"7"},{"id":10,"sheetLink":"13zbPhkw6Wccwa9QPvUYFKEcEvLqHk9c9KY-9EQkMqo0","sheetName":"Eva - Module Template V1.0 - CoronaGo","tab":"Data Model","type":"Warning","problem":"Allowed values are missing for `Meeting Url`","solution":"For Data type Checkbox/CheckboxGroup/DropDown/RadioButton/Multiselect allowed values should be configured","rowIdx":"48","column":"7"},{"id":11,"sheetLink":"13zbPhkw6Wccwa9QPvUYFKEcEvLqHk9c9KY-9EQkMqo0","sheetName":"Eva - Module Template V1.0 - CoronaGo","tab":"Data Model","type":"Warning","problem":"Allowed values are missing for `Doctor Name`","solution":"For Data type Checkbox/CheckboxGroup/DropDown/RadioButton/Multiselect allowed values should be configured","rowIdx":"52","column":"7"},{"id":12,"sheetLink":"13zbPhkw6Wccwa9QPvUYFKEcEvLqHk9c9KY-9EQkMqo0","sheetName":"Eva - Module Template V1.0 - CoronaGo","tab":"Data Model","type":"Warning","problem":"Allowed values are missing for `Item`","solution":"For Data type Checkbox/CheckboxGroup/DropDown/RadioButton/Multiselect allowed values should be configured","rowIdx":"56","column":"7"},{"id":13,"sheetLink":"13zbPhkw6Wccwa9QPvUYFKEcEvLqHk9c9KY-9EQkMqo0","sheetName":"Eva - Module Template V1.0 - CoronaGo","tab":"Data Model","type":"Warning","problem":"Allowed values are missing for `Patient Name`","solution":"For Data type Checkbox/CheckboxGroup/DropDown/RadioButton/Multiselect allowed values should be configured","rowIdx":"74","column":"7"},{"id":14,"sheetLink":"13zbPhkw6Wccwa9QPvUYFKEcEvLqHk9c9KY-9EQkMqo0","sheetName":"Eva - Module Template V1.0 - CoronaGo","tab":"Data Model","type":"Warning","problem":"Allowed values are missing for `Patient HId`","solution":"For Data type Checkbox/CheckboxGroup/DropDown/RadioButton/Multiselect allowed values should be configured","rowIdx":"76","column":"7"},{"id":15,"sheetLink":"13zbPhkw6Wccwa9QPvUYFKEcEvLqHk9c9KY-9EQkMqo0","sheetName":"Eva - Module Template V1.0 - CoronaGo","tab":"Data Model","type":"Warning","problem":"Allowed values are missing for `City`","solution":"For Data type Checkbox/CheckboxGroup/DropDown/RadioButton/Multiselect allowed values should be configured","rowIdx":"81","column":"7"},{"id":16,"sheetLink":"13zbPhkw6Wccwa9QPvUYFKEcEvLqHk9c9KY-9EQkMqo0","sheetName":"Eva - Module Template V1.0 - CoronaGo","tab":"Data Model","type":"Warning","problem":"Allowed values are missing for `Insurance Provider`","solution":"For Data type Checkbox/CheckboxGroup/DropDown/RadioButton/Multiselect allowed values should be configured","rowIdx":"83","column":"7"},{"id":17,"sheetLink":"13zbPhkw6Wccwa9QPvUYFKEcEvLqHk9c9KY-9EQkMqo0","sheetName":"Eva - Module Template V1.0 - CoronaGo","tab":"Data Model","type":"Warning","problem":"Allowed values are missing for `Patient Name`","solution":"For Data type Checkbox/CheckboxGroup/DropDown/RadioButton/Multiselect allowed values should be configured","rowIdx":"6","column":"7"},{"id":18,"sheetLink":"13zbPhkw6Wccwa9QPvUYFKEcEvLqHk9c9KY-9EQkMqo0","sheetName":"Eva - Module Template V1.0 - CoronaGo","tab":"Data Model","type":"Warning","problem":"Allowed values are missing for `Patient HId`","solution":"For Data type Checkbox/CheckboxGroup/DropDown/RadioButton/Multiselect allowed values should be configured","rowIdx":"8","column":"7"},{"id":19,"sheetLink":"13zbPhkw6Wccwa9QPvUYFKEcEvLqHk9c9KY-9EQkMqo0","sheetName":"Eva - Module Template V1.0 - CoronaGo","tab":"List Pages","type":"Warning","problem":"Column field `Date of Birth` not found in datamodel","solution":"Configure value for the column in list page","rowIdx":"4","column":"6"},{"id":20,"sheetLink":"13zbPhkw6Wccwa9QPvUYFKEcEvLqHk9c9KY-9EQkMqo0","sheetName":"Eva - Module Template V1.0 - CoronaGo","tab":"List Pages","type":"Warning","problem":"Column field `Date of Birth` not found in datamodel","solution":"Configure value for the column in list page","rowIdx":"4","column":"6"},{"id":21,"sheetLink":"13zbPhkw6Wccwa9QPvUYFKEcEvLqHk9c9KY-9EQkMqo0","sheetName":"Eva - Module Template V1.0 - CoronaGo","tab":"List Pages","type":"Warning","problem":"Column field `Date of Birth` not found in datamodel","solution":"Configure value for the column in list page","rowIdx":"5","column":"6"},{"id":22,"sheetLink":"13zbPhkw6Wccwa9QPvUYFKEcEvLqHk9c9KY-9EQkMqo0","sheetName":"Eva - Module Template V1.0 - CoronaGo","tab":"List Pages","type":"Warning","problem":"Column field `Date of Birth` not found in datamodel","solution":"Configure value for the column in list page","rowIdx":"5","column":"6"},{"id":23,"sheetLink":"13zbPhkw6Wccwa9QPvUYFKEcEvLqHk9c9KY-9EQkMqo0","sheetName":"Eva - Module Template V1.0 - CoronaGo","tab":"List Pages","type":"Warning","problem":"Column field `Date of Birth` not found in datamodel","solution":"Configure value for the column in list page","rowIdx":"6","column":"6"},{"id":24,"sheetLink":"13zbPhkw6Wccwa9QPvUYFKEcEvLqHk9c9KY-9EQkMqo0","sheetName":"Eva - Module Template V1.0 - CoronaGo","tab":"List Pages","type":"Warning","problem":"Column field `Date of Birth` not found in datamodel","solution":"Configure value for the column in list page","rowIdx":"6","column":"6"},{"id":25,"sheetLink":"13zbPhkw6Wccwa9QPvUYFKEcEvLqHk9c9KY-9EQkMqo0","sheetName":"Eva - Module Template V1.0 - CoronaGo","tab":"List Pages","type":"Warning","problem":"Column field `Date of Birth` not found in datamodel","solution":"Configure value for the column in list page","rowIdx":"7","column":"6"},{"id":26,"sheetLink":"13zbPhkw6Wccwa9QPvUYFKEcEvLqHk9c9KY-9EQkMqo0","sheetName":"Eva - Module Template V1.0 - CoronaGo","tab":"List Pages","type":"Warning","problem":"Column field `Date of Birth` not found in datamodel","solution":"Configure value for the column in list page","rowIdx":"7","column":"6"},{"id":27,"sheetLink":"13zbPhkw6Wccwa9QPvUYFKEcEvLqHk9c9KY-9EQkMqo0","sheetName":"Eva - Module Template V1.0 - CoronaGo","tab":"List Pages","type":"Warning","problem":"Column field `Date of Birth` not found in datamodel","solution":"Configure value for the column in list page","rowIdx":"8","column":"6"},{"id":28,"sheetLink":"13zbPhkw6Wccwa9QPvUYFKEcEvLqHk9c9KY-9EQkMqo0","sheetName":"Eva - Module Template V1.0 - CoronaGo","tab":"List Pages","type":"Warning","problem":"Column field `Date of Birth` not found in datamodel","solution":"Configure value for the column in list page","rowIdx":"8","column":"6"}]},{"id":7,"action":"Detail Page Generation","dateTime":1585117875610,"items":[{"id":1,"sheetLink":"13zbPhkw6Wccwa9QPvUYFKEcEvLqHk9c9KY-9EQkMqo0","sheetName":"Eva - Module Template V1.0 - CoronaGo","tab":"Data Model","type":"Warning","problem":"Allowed values are missing for `Hospital Name`","solution":"For Data type Checkbox/CheckboxGroup/DropDown/RadioButton/Multiselect allowed values should be configured","rowIdx":"59","column":"7"},{"id":2,"sheetLink":"13zbPhkw6Wccwa9QPvUYFKEcEvLqHk9c9KY-9EQkMqo0","sheetName":"Eva - Module Template V1.0 - CoronaGo","tab":"Data Model","type":"Warning","problem":"Allowed values are missing for `Item`","solution":"For Data type Checkbox/CheckboxGroup/DropDown/RadioButton/Multiselect allowed values should be configured","rowIdx":"60","column":"7"},{"id":3,"sheetLink":"13zbPhkw6Wccwa9QPvUYFKEcEvLqHk9c9KY-9EQkMqo0","sheetName":"Eva - Module Template V1.0 - CoronaGo","tab":"Data Model","type":"Warning","problem":"Allowed values are missing for `Item`","solution":"For Data type Checkbox/CheckboxGroup/DropDown/RadioButton/Multiselect allowed values should be configured","rowIdx":"63","column":"7"},{"id":4,"sheetLink":"13zbPhkw6Wccwa9QPvUYFKEcEvLqHk9c9KY-9EQkMqo0","sheetName":"Eva - Module Template V1.0 - CoronaGo","tab":"Data Model","type":"Warning","problem":"Allowed values are missing for `Patient Hid`","solution":"For Data type Checkbox/CheckboxGroup/DropDown/RadioButton/Multiselect allowed values should be configured","rowIdx":"38","column":"7"},{"id":5,"sheetLink":"13zbPhkw6Wccwa9QPvUYFKEcEvLqHk9c9KY-9EQkMqo0","sheetName":"Eva - Module Template V1.0 - CoronaGo","tab":"Data Model","type":"Warning","problem":"Allowed values are missing for `Patient Name`","solution":"For Data type Checkbox/CheckboxGroup/DropDown/RadioButton/Multiselect allowed values should be configured","rowIdx":"39","column":"7"},{"id":6,"sheetLink":"13zbPhkw6Wccwa9QPvUYFKEcEvLqHk9c9KY-9EQkMqo0","sheetName":"Eva - Module Template V1.0 - CoronaGo","tab":"Data Model","type":"Warning","problem":"Allowed values are missing for `Meeting Id`","solution":"For Data type Checkbox/CheckboxGroup/DropDown/RadioButton/Multiselect allowed values should be configured","rowIdx":"41","column":"7"},{"id":7,"sheetLink":"13zbPhkw6Wccwa9QPvUYFKEcEvLqHk9c9KY-9EQkMqo0","sheetName":"Eva - Module Template V1.0 - CoronaGo","tab":"Data Model","type":"Warning","problem":"Allowed values are missing for `Doctor Id`","solution":"For Data type Checkbox/CheckboxGroup/DropDown/RadioButton/Multiselect allowed values should be configured","rowIdx":"42","column":"7"},{"id":8,"sheetLink":"13zbPhkw6Wccwa9QPvUYFKEcEvLqHk9c9KY-9EQkMqo0","sheetName":"Eva - Module Template V1.0 - CoronaGo","tab":"Data Model","type":"Warning","problem":"Allowed values are missing for `Doctor Name`","solution":"For Data type Checkbox/CheckboxGroup/DropDown/RadioButton/Multiselect allowed values should be configured","rowIdx":"43","column":"7"},{"id":9,"sheetLink":"13zbPhkw6Wccwa9QPvUYFKEcEvLqHk9c9KY-9EQkMqo0","sheetName":"Eva - Module Template V1.0 - CoronaGo","tab":"Data Model","type":"Warning","problem":"Allowed values are missing for `Meeting Status`","solution":"For Data type Checkbox/CheckboxGroup/DropDown/RadioButton/Multiselect allowed values should be configured","rowIdx":"47","column":"7"},{"id":10,"sheetLink":"13zbPhkw6Wccwa9QPvUYFKEcEvLqHk9c9KY-9EQkMqo0","sheetName":"Eva - Module Template V1.0 - CoronaGo","tab":"Data Model","type":"Warning","problem":"Allowed values are missing for `Meeting Url`","solution":"For Data type Checkbox/CheckboxGroup/DropDown/RadioButton/Multiselect allowed values should be configured","rowIdx":"48","column":"7"},{"id":11,"sheetLink":"13zbPhkw6Wccwa9QPvUYFKEcEvLqHk9c9KY-9EQkMqo0","sheetName":"Eva - Module Template V1.0 - CoronaGo","tab":"Data Model","type":"Warning","problem":"Allowed values are missing for `Doctor Name`","solution":"For Data type Checkbox/CheckboxGroup/DropDown/RadioButton/Multiselect allowed values should be configured","rowIdx":"52","column":"7"},{"id":12,"sheetLink":"13zbPhkw6Wccwa9QPvUYFKEcEvLqHk9c9KY-9EQkMqo0","sheetName":"Eva - Module Template V1.0 - CoronaGo","tab":"Data Model","type":"Warning","problem":"Allowed values are missing for `Item`","solution":"For Data type Checkbox/CheckboxGroup/DropDown/RadioButton/Multiselect allowed values should be configured","rowIdx":"56","column":"7"},{"id":13,"sheetLink":"13zbPhkw6Wccwa9QPvUYFKEcEvLqHk9c9KY-9EQkMqo0","sheetName":"Eva - Module Template V1.0 - CoronaGo","tab":"Data Model","type":"Warning","problem":"Allowed values are missing for `Patient Name`","solution":"For Data type Checkbox/CheckboxGroup/DropDown/RadioButton/Multiselect allowed values should be configured","rowIdx":"74","column":"7"},{"id":14,"sheetLink":"13zbPhkw6Wccwa9QPvUYFKEcEvLqHk9c9KY-9EQkMqo0","sheetName":"Eva - Module Template V1.0 - CoronaGo","tab":"Data Model","type":"Warning","problem":"Allowed values are missing for `Patient HId`","solution":"For Data type Checkbox/CheckboxGroup/DropDown/RadioButton/Multiselect allowed values should be configured","rowIdx":"76","column":"7"},{"id":15,"sheetLink":"13zbPhkw6Wccwa9QPvUYFKEcEvLqHk9c9KY-9EQkMqo0","sheetName":"Eva - Module Template V1.0 - CoronaGo","tab":"Data Model","type":"Warning","problem":"Allowed values are missing for `City`","solution":"For Data type Checkbox/CheckboxGroup/DropDown/RadioButton/Multiselect allowed values should be configured","rowIdx":"81","column":"7"},{"id":16,"sheetLink":"13zbPhkw6Wccwa9QPvUYFKEcEvLqHk9c9KY-9EQkMqo0","sheetName":"Eva - Module Template V1.0 - CoronaGo","tab":"Data Model","type":"Warning","problem":"Allowed values are missing for `Insurance Provider`","solution":"For Data type Checkbox/CheckboxGroup/DropDown/RadioButton/Multiselect allowed values should be configured","rowIdx":"83","column":"7"},{"id":17,"sheetLink":"13zbPhkw6Wccwa9QPvUYFKEcEvLqHk9c9KY-9EQkMqo0","sheetName":"Eva - Module Template V1.0 - CoronaGo","tab":"Data Model","type":"Warning","problem":"Allowed values are missing for `Patient Name`","solution":"For Data type Checkbox/CheckboxGroup/DropDown/RadioButton/Multiselect allowed values should be configured","rowIdx":"6","column":"7"},{"id":18,"sheetLink":"13zbPhkw6Wccwa9QPvUYFKEcEvLqHk9c9KY-9EQkMqo0","sheetName":"Eva - Module Template V1.0 - CoronaGo","tab":"Data Model","type":"Warning","problem":"Allowed values are missing for `Patient HId`","solution":"For Data type Checkbox/CheckboxGroup/DropDown/RadioButton/Multiselect allowed values should be configured","rowIdx":"8","column":"7"},{"id":19,"sheetLink":"13zbPhkw6Wccwa9QPvUYFKEcEvLqHk9c9KY-9EQkMqo0","sheetName":"Eva - Module Template V1.0 - CoronaGo","tab":"List Pages","type":"Warning","problem":"Column field `Date of Birth` not found in datamodel","solution":"Configure value for the column in list page","rowIdx":"4","column":"6"},{"id":20,"sheetLink":"13zbPhkw6Wccwa9QPvUYFKEcEvLqHk9c9KY-9EQkMqo0","sheetName":"Eva - Module Template V1.0 - CoronaGo","tab":"List Pages","type":"Warning","problem":"Column field `Date of Birth` not found in datamodel","solution":"Configure value for the column in list page","rowIdx":"4","column":"6"},{"id":21,"sheetLink":"13zbPhkw6Wccwa9QPvUYFKEcEvLqHk9c9KY-9EQkMqo0","sheetName":"Eva - Module Template V1.0 - CoronaGo","tab":"List Pages","type":"Warning","problem":"Column field `Date of Birth` not found in datamodel","solution":"Configure value for the column in list page","rowIdx":"5","column":"6"},{"id":22,"sheetLink":"13zbPhkw6Wccwa9QPvUYFKEcEvLqHk9c9KY-9EQkMqo0","sheetName":"Eva - Module Template V1.0 - CoronaGo","tab":"List Pages","type":"Warning","problem":"Column field `Date of Birth` not found in datamodel","solution":"Configure value for the column in list page","rowIdx":"5","column":"6"},{"id":23,"sheetLink":"13zbPhkw6Wccwa9QPvUYFKEcEvLqHk9c9KY-9EQkMqo0","sheetName":"Eva - Module Template V1.0 - CoronaGo","tab":"List Pages","type":"Warning","problem":"Column field `Date of Birth` not found in datamodel","solution":"Configure value for the column in list page","rowIdx":"6","column":"6"},{"id":24,"sheetLink":"13zbPhkw6Wccwa9QPvUYFKEcEvLqHk9c9KY-9EQkMqo0","sheetName":"Eva - Module Template V1.0 - CoronaGo","tab":"List Pages","type":"Warning","problem":"Column field `Date of Birth` not found in datamodel","solution":"Configure value for the column in list page","rowIdx":"6","column":"6"},{"id":25,"sheetLink":"13zbPhkw6Wccwa9QPvUYFKEcEvLqHk9c9KY-9EQkMqo0","sheetName":"Eva - Module Template V1.0 - CoronaGo","tab":"List Pages","type":"Warning","problem":"Column field `Date of Birth` not found in datamodel","solution":"Configure value for the column in list page","rowIdx":"7","column":"6"},{"id":26,"sheetLink":"13zbPhkw6Wccwa9QPvUYFKEcEvLqHk9c9KY-9EQkMqo0","sheetName":"Eva - Module Template V1.0 - CoronaGo","tab":"List Pages","type":"Warning","problem":"Column field `Date of Birth` not found in datamodel","solution":"Configure value for the column in list page","rowIdx":"7","column":"6"},{"id":27,"sheetLink":"13zbPhkw6Wccwa9QPvUYFKEcEvLqHk9c9KY-9EQkMqo0","sheetName":"Eva - Module Template V1.0 - CoronaGo","tab":"List Pages","type":"Warning","problem":"Column field `Date of Birth` not found in datamodel","solution":"Configure value for the column in list page","rowIdx":"8","column":"6"},{"id":28,"sheetLink":"13zbPhkw6Wccwa9QPvUYFKEcEvLqHk9c9KY-9EQkMqo0","sheetName":"Eva - Module Template V1.0 - CoronaGo","tab":"List Pages","type":"Warning","problem":"Column field `Date of Birth` not found in datamodel","solution":"Configure value for the column in list page","rowIdx":"8","column":"6"}]},{"id":8,"action":"Tabs Generation","dateTime":1585117419437,"items":[{"id":1,"sheetLink":"13zbPhkw6Wccwa9QPvUYFKEcEvLqHk9c9KY-9EQkMqo0","sheetName":"Eva - Module Template V1.0 - CoronaGo","tab":"Data Model","type":"Warning","problem":"Allowed values are missing for `Hospital Name`","solution":"For Data type Checkbox/CheckboxGroup/DropDown/RadioButton/Multiselect allowed values should be configured","rowIdx":"59","column":"7"},{"id":2,"sheetLink":"13zbPhkw6Wccwa9QPvUYFKEcEvLqHk9c9KY-9EQkMqo0","sheetName":"Eva - Module Template V1.0 - CoronaGo","tab":"Data Model","type":"Warning","problem":"Allowed values are missing for `Item`","solution":"For Data type Checkbox/CheckboxGroup/DropDown/RadioButton/Multiselect allowed values should be configured","rowIdx":"60","column":"7"},{"id":3,"sheetLink":"13zbPhkw6Wccwa9QPvUYFKEcEvLqHk9c9KY-9EQkMqo0","sheetName":"Eva - Module Template V1.0 - CoronaGo","tab":"Data Model","type":"Warning","problem":"Allowed values are missing for `Item`","solution":"For Data type Checkbox/CheckboxGroup/DropDown/RadioButton/Multiselect allowed values should be configured","rowIdx":"63","column":"7"},{"id":4,"sheetLink":"13zbPhkw6Wccwa9QPvUYFKEcEvLqHk9c9KY-9EQkMqo0","sheetName":"Eva - Module Template V1.0 - CoronaGo","tab":"Data Model","type":"Warning","problem":"Allowed values are missing for `Patient Hid`","solution":"For Data type Checkbox/CheckboxGroup/DropDown/RadioButton/Multiselect allowed values should be configured","rowIdx":"38","column":"7"},{"id":5,"sheetLink":"13zbPhkw6Wccwa9QPvUYFKEcEvLqHk9c9KY-9EQkMqo0","sheetName":"Eva - Module Template V1.0 - CoronaGo","tab":"Data Model","type":"Warning","problem":"Allowed values are missing for `Patient Name`","solution":"For Data type Checkbox/CheckboxGroup/DropDown/RadioButton/Multiselect allowed values should be configured","rowIdx":"39","column":"7"},{"id":6,"sheetLink":"13zbPhkw6Wccwa9QPvUYFKEcEvLqHk9c9KY-9EQkMqo0","sheetName":"Eva - Module Template V1.0 - CoronaGo","tab":"Data Model","type":"Warning","problem":"Allowed values are missing for `Meeting Id`","solution":"For Data type Checkbox/CheckboxGroup/DropDown/RadioButton/Multiselect allowed values should be configured","rowIdx":"41","column":"7"},{"id":7,"sheetLink":"13zbPhkw6Wccwa9QPvUYFKEcEvLqHk9c9KY-9EQkMqo0","sheetName":"Eva - Module Template V1.0 - CoronaGo","tab":"Data Model","type":"Warning","problem":"Allowed values are missing for `Doctor Id`","solution":"For Data type Checkbox/CheckboxGroup/DropDown/RadioButton/Multiselect allowed values should be configured","rowIdx":"42","column":"7"},{"id":8,"sheetLink":"13zbPhkw6Wccwa9QPvUYFKEcEvLqHk9c9KY-9EQkMqo0","sheetName":"Eva - Module Template V1.0 - CoronaGo","tab":"Data Model","type":"Warning","problem":"Allowed values are missing for `Doctor Name`","solution":"For Data type Checkbox/CheckboxGroup/DropDown/RadioButton/Multiselect allowed values should be configured","rowIdx":"43","column":"7"},{"id":9,"sheetLink":"13zbPhkw6Wccwa9QPvUYFKEcEvLqHk9c9KY-9EQkMqo0","sheetName":"Eva - Module Template V1.0 - CoronaGo","tab":"Data Model","type":"Warning","problem":"Allowed values are missing for `Meeting Status`","solution":"For Data type Checkbox/CheckboxGroup/DropDown/RadioButton/Multiselect allowed values should be configured","rowIdx":"47","column":"7"},{"id":10,"sheetLink":"13zbPhkw6Wccwa9QPvUYFKEcEvLqHk9c9KY-9EQkMqo0","sheetName":"Eva - Module Template V1.0 - CoronaGo","tab":"Data Model","type":"Warning","problem":"Allowed values are missing for `Meeting Url`","solution":"For Data type Checkbox/CheckboxGroup/DropDown/RadioButton/Multiselect allowed values should be configured","rowIdx":"48","column":"7"},{"id":11,"sheetLink":"13zbPhkw6Wccwa9QPvUYFKEcEvLqHk9c9KY-9EQkMqo0","sheetName":"Eva - Module Template V1.0 - CoronaGo","tab":"Data Model","type":"Warning","problem":"Allowed values are missing for `Doctor Name`","solution":"For Data type Checkbox/CheckboxGroup/DropDown/RadioButton/Multiselect allowed values should be configured","rowIdx":"52","column":"7"},{"id":12,"sheetLink":"13zbPhkw6Wccwa9QPvUYFKEcEvLqHk9c9KY-9EQkMqo0","sheetName":"Eva - Module Template V1.0 - CoronaGo","tab":"Data Model","type":"Warning","problem":"Allowed values are missing for `Item`","solution":"For Data type Checkbox/CheckboxGroup/DropDown/RadioButton/Multiselect allowed values should be configured","rowIdx":"56","column":"7"},{"id":13,"sheetLink":"13zbPhkw6Wccwa9QPvUYFKEcEvLqHk9c9KY-9EQkMqo0","sheetName":"Eva - Module Template V1.0 - CoronaGo","tab":"Data Model","type":"Warning","problem":"Allowed values are missing for `Patient Name`","solution":"For Data type Checkbox/CheckboxGroup/DropDown/RadioButton/Multiselect allowed values should be configured","rowIdx":"74","column":"7"},{"id":14,"sheetLink":"13zbPhkw6Wccwa9QPvUYFKEcEvLqHk9c9KY-9EQkMqo0","sheetName":"Eva - Module Template V1.0 - CoronaGo","tab":"Data Model","type":"Warning","problem":"Allowed values are missing for `Patient HId`","solution":"For Data type Checkbox/CheckboxGroup/DropDown/RadioButton/Multiselect allowed values should be configured","rowIdx":"76","column":"7"},{"id":15,"sheetLink":"13zbPhkw6Wccwa9QPvUYFKEcEvLqHk9c9KY-9EQkMqo0","sheetName":"Eva - Module Template V1.0 - CoronaGo","tab":"Data Model","type":"Warning","problem":"Allowed values are missing for `City`","solution":"For Data type Checkbox/CheckboxGroup/DropDown/RadioButton/Multiselect allowed values should be configured","rowIdx":"81","column":"7"},{"id":16,"sheetLink":"13zbPhkw6Wccwa9QPvUYFKEcEvLqHk9c9KY-9EQkMqo0","sheetName":"Eva - Module Template V1.0 - CoronaGo","tab":"Data Model","type":"Warning","problem":"Allowed values are missing for `Insurance Provider`","solution":"For Data type Checkbox/CheckboxGroup/DropDown/RadioButton/Multiselect allowed values should be configured","rowIdx":"83","column":"7"},{"id":17,"sheetLink":"13zbPhkw6Wccwa9QPvUYFKEcEvLqHk9c9KY-9EQkMqo0","sheetName":"Eva - Module Template V1.0 - CoronaGo","tab":"Data Model","type":"Warning","problem":"Allowed values are missing for `Patient Name`","solution":"For Data type Checkbox/CheckboxGroup/DropDown/RadioButton/Multiselect allowed values should be configured","rowIdx":"6","column":"7"},{"id":18,"sheetLink":"13zbPhkw6Wccwa9QPvUYFKEcEvLqHk9c9KY-9EQkMqo0","sheetName":"Eva - Module Template V1.0 - CoronaGo","tab":"Data Model","type":"Warning","problem":"Allowed values are missing for `Patient HId`","solution":"For Data type Checkbox/CheckboxGroup/DropDown/RadioButton/Multiselect allowed values should be configured","rowIdx":"8","column":"7"},{"id":19,"sheetLink":"13zbPhkw6Wccwa9QPvUYFKEcEvLqHk9c9KY-9EQkMqo0","sheetName":"Eva - Module Template V1.0 - CoronaGo","tab":"List Pages","type":"Warning","problem":"Column field `Date of Birth` not found in datamodel","solution":"Configure value for the column in list page","rowIdx":"4","column":"6"},{"id":20,"sheetLink":"13zbPhkw6Wccwa9QPvUYFKEcEvLqHk9c9KY-9EQkMqo0","sheetName":"Eva - Module Template V1.0 - CoronaGo","tab":"List Pages","type":"Warning","problem":"Column field `Date of Birth` not found in datamodel","solution":"Configure value for the column in list page","rowIdx":"4","column":"6"},{"id":21,"sheetLink":"13zbPhkw6Wccwa9QPvUYFKEcEvLqHk9c9KY-9EQkMqo0","sheetName":"Eva - Module Template V1.0 - CoronaGo","tab":"List Pages","type":"Warning","problem":"Column field `Date of Birth` not found in datamodel","solution":"Configure value for the column in list page","rowIdx":"5","column":"6"},{"id":22,"sheetLink":"13zbPhkw6Wccwa9QPvUYFKEcEvLqHk9c9KY-9EQkMqo0","sheetName":"Eva - Module Template V1.0 - CoronaGo","tab":"List Pages","type":"Warning","problem":"Column field `Date of Birth` not found in datamodel","solution":"Configure value for the column in list page","rowIdx":"5","column":"6"},{"id":23,"sheetLink":"13zbPhkw6Wccwa9QPvUYFKEcEvLqHk9c9KY-9EQkMqo0","sheetName":"Eva - Module Template V1.0 - CoronaGo","tab":"List Pages","type":"Warning","problem":"Column field `Date of Birth` not found in datamodel","solution":"Configure value for the column in list page","rowIdx":"6","column":"6"},{"id":24,"sheetLink":"13zbPhkw6Wccwa9QPvUYFKEcEvLqHk9c9KY-9EQkMqo0","sheetName":"Eva - Module Template V1.0 - CoronaGo","tab":"List Pages","type":"Warning","problem":"Column field `Date of Birth` not found in datamodel","solution":"Configure value for the column in list page","rowIdx":"6","column":"6"},{"id":25,"sheetLink":"13zbPhkw6Wccwa9QPvUYFKEcEvLqHk9c9KY-9EQkMqo0","sheetName":"Eva - Module Template V1.0 - CoronaGo","tab":"List Pages","type":"Warning","problem":"Column field `Date of Birth` not found in datamodel","solution":"Configure value for the column in list page","rowIdx":"7","column":"6"},{"id":26,"sheetLink":"13zbPhkw6Wccwa9QPvUYFKEcEvLqHk9c9KY-9EQkMqo0","sheetName":"Eva - Module Template V1.0 - CoronaGo","tab":"List Pages","type":"Warning","problem":"Column field `Date of Birth` not found in datamodel","solution":"Configure value for the column in list page","rowIdx":"7","column":"6"},{"id":27,"sheetLink":"13zbPhkw6Wccwa9QPvUYFKEcEvLqHk9c9KY-9EQkMqo0","sheetName":"Eva - Module Template V1.0 - CoronaGo","tab":"List Pages","type":"Warning","problem":"Column field `Date of Birth` not found in datamodel","solution":"Configure value for the column in list page","rowIdx":"8","column":"6"},{"id":28,"sheetLink":"13zbPhkw6Wccwa9QPvUYFKEcEvLqHk9c9KY-9EQkMqo0","sheetName":"Eva - Module Template V1.0 - CoronaGo","tab":"List Pages","type":"Warning","problem":"Column field `Date of Birth` not found in datamodel","solution":"Configure value for the column in list page","rowIdx":"8","column":"6"}]},{"id":9,"action":"Detail Page Generation","dateTime":1585117373725,"items":[{"id":1,"sheetLink":"13zbPhkw6Wccwa9QPvUYFKEcEvLqHk9c9KY-9EQkMqo0","sheetName":"Eva - Module Template V1.0 - CoronaGo","tab":"Data Model","type":"Warning","problem":"Allowed values are missing for `Hospital Name`","solution":"For Data type Checkbox/CheckboxGroup/DropDown/RadioButton/Multiselect allowed values should be configured","rowIdx":"59","column":"7"},{"id":2,"sheetLink":"13zbPhkw6Wccwa9QPvUYFKEcEvLqHk9c9KY-9EQkMqo0","sheetName":"Eva - Module Template V1.0 - CoronaGo","tab":"Data Model","type":"Warning","problem":"Allowed values are missing for `Item`","solution":"For Data type Checkbox/CheckboxGroup/DropDown/RadioButton/Multiselect allowed values should be configured","rowIdx":"60","column":"7"},{"id":3,"sheetLink":"13zbPhkw6Wccwa9QPvUYFKEcEvLqHk9c9KY-9EQkMqo0","sheetName":"Eva - Module Template V1.0 - CoronaGo","tab":"Data Model","type":"Warning","problem":"Allowed values are missing for `Item`","solution":"For Data type Checkbox/CheckboxGroup/DropDown/RadioButton/Multiselect allowed values should be configured","rowIdx":"63","column":"7"},{"id":4,"sheetLink":"13zbPhkw6Wccwa9QPvUYFKEcEvLqHk9c9KY-9EQkMqo0","sheetName":"Eva - Module Template V1.0 - CoronaGo","tab":"Data Model","type":"Warning","problem":"Allowed values are missing for `Patient Hid`","solution":"For Data type Checkbox/CheckboxGroup/DropDown/RadioButton/Multiselect allowed values should be configured","rowIdx":"38","column":"7"},{"id":5,"sheetLink":"13zbPhkw6Wccwa9QPvUYFKEcEvLqHk9c9KY-9EQkMqo0","sheetName":"Eva - Module Template V1.0 - CoronaGo","tab":"Data Model","type":"Warning","problem":"Allowed values are missing for `Patient Name`","solution":"For Data type Checkbox/CheckboxGroup/DropDown/RadioButton/Multiselect allowed values should be configured","rowIdx":"39","column":"7"},{"id":6,"sheetLink":"13zbPhkw6Wccwa9QPvUYFKEcEvLqHk9c9KY-9EQkMqo0","sheetName":"Eva - Module Template V1.0 - CoronaGo","tab":"Data Model","type":"Warning","problem":"Allowed values are missing for `Meeting Id`","solution":"For Data type Checkbox/CheckboxGroup/DropDown/RadioButton/Multiselect allowed values should be configured","rowIdx":"41","column":"7"},{"id":7,"sheetLink":"13zbPhkw6Wccwa9QPvUYFKEcEvLqHk9c9KY-9EQkMqo0","sheetName":"Eva - Module Template V1.0 - CoronaGo","tab":"Data Model","type":"Warning","problem":"Allowed values are missing for `Doctor Id`","solution":"For Data type Checkbox/CheckboxGroup/DropDown/RadioButton/Multiselect allowed values should be configured","rowIdx":"42","column":"7"},{"id":8,"sheetLink":"13zbPhkw6Wccwa9QPvUYFKEcEvLqHk9c9KY-9EQkMqo0","sheetName":"Eva - Module Template V1.0 - CoronaGo","tab":"Data Model","type":"Warning","problem":"Allowed values are missing for `Doctor Name`","solution":"For Data type Checkbox/CheckboxGroup/DropDown/RadioButton/Multiselect allowed values should be configured","rowIdx":"43","column":"7"},{"id":9,"sheetLink":"13zbPhkw6Wccwa9QPvUYFKEcEvLqHk9c9KY-9EQkMqo0","sheetName":"Eva - Module Template V1.0 - CoronaGo","tab":"Data Model","type":"Warning","problem":"Allowed values are missing for `Meeting Status`","solution":"For Data type Checkbox/CheckboxGroup/DropDown/RadioButton/Multiselect allowed values should be configured","rowIdx":"47","column":"7"},{"id":10,"sheetLink":"13zbPhkw6Wccwa9QPvUYFKEcEvLqHk9c9KY-9EQkMqo0","sheetName":"Eva - Module Template V1.0 - CoronaGo","tab":"Data Model","type":"Warning","problem":"Allowed values are missing for `Meeting Url`","solution":"For Data type Checkbox/CheckboxGroup/DropDown/RadioButton/Multiselect allowed values should be configured","rowIdx":"48","column":"7"},{"id":11,"sheetLink":"13zbPhkw6Wccwa9QPvUYFKEcEvLqHk9c9KY-9EQkMqo0","sheetName":"Eva - Module Template V1.0 - CoronaGo","tab":"Data Model","type":"Warning","problem":"Allowed values are missing for `Doctor Name`","solution":"For Data type Checkbox/CheckboxGroup/DropDown/RadioButton/Multiselect allowed values should be configured","rowIdx":"52","column":"7"},{"id":12,"sheetLink":"13zbPhkw6Wccwa9QPvUYFKEcEvLqHk9c9KY-9EQkMqo0","sheetName":"Eva - Module Template V1.0 - CoronaGo","tab":"Data Model","type":"Warning","problem":"Allowed values are missing for `Item`","solution":"For Data type Checkbox/CheckboxGroup/DropDown/RadioButton/Multiselect allowed values should be configured","rowIdx":"56","column":"7"},{"id":13,"sheetLink":"13zbPhkw6Wccwa9QPvUYFKEcEvLqHk9c9KY-9EQkMqo0","sheetName":"Eva - Module Template V1.0 - CoronaGo","tab":"Data Model","type":"Warning","problem":"Allowed values are missing for `Patient Name`","solution":"For Data type Checkbox/CheckboxGroup/DropDown/RadioButton/Multiselect allowed values should be configured","rowIdx":"74","column":"7"},{"id":14,"sheetLink":"13zbPhkw6Wccwa9QPvUYFKEcEvLqHk9c9KY-9EQkMqo0","sheetName":"Eva - Module Template V1.0 - CoronaGo","tab":"Data Model","type":"Warning","problem":"Allowed values are missing for `Patient HId`","solution":"For Data type Checkbox/CheckboxGroup/DropDown/RadioButton/Multiselect allowed values should be configured","rowIdx":"76","column":"7"},{"id":15,"sheetLink":"13zbPhkw6Wccwa9QPvUYFKEcEvLqHk9c9KY-9EQkMqo0","sheetName":"Eva - Module Template V1.0 - CoronaGo","tab":"Data Model","type":"Warning","problem":"Allowed values are missing for `City`","solution":"For Data type Checkbox/CheckboxGroup/DropDown/RadioButton/Multiselect allowed values should be configured","rowIdx":"81","column":"7"},{"id":16,"sheetLink":"13zbPhkw6Wccwa9QPvUYFKEcEvLqHk9c9KY-9EQkMqo0","sheetName":"Eva - Module Template V1.0 - CoronaGo","tab":"Data Model","type":"Warning","problem":"Allowed values are missing for `Insurance Provider`","solution":"For Data type Checkbox/CheckboxGroup/DropDown/RadioButton/Multiselect allowed values should be configured","rowIdx":"83","column":"7"},{"id":17,"sheetLink":"13zbPhkw6Wccwa9QPvUYFKEcEvLqHk9c9KY-9EQkMqo0","sheetName":"Eva - Module Template V1.0 - CoronaGo","tab":"Data Model","type":"Warning","problem":"Allowed values are missing for `Patient Name`","solution":"For Data type Checkbox/CheckboxGroup/DropDown/RadioButton/Multiselect allowed values should be configured","rowIdx":"6","column":"7"},{"id":18,"sheetLink":"13zbPhkw6Wccwa9QPvUYFKEcEvLqHk9c9KY-9EQkMqo0","sheetName":"Eva - Module Template V1.0 - CoronaGo","tab":"Data Model","type":"Warning","problem":"Allowed values are missing for `Patient HId`","solution":"For Data type Checkbox/CheckboxGroup/DropDown/RadioButton/Multiselect allowed values should be configured","rowIdx":"8","column":"7"},{"id":19,"sheetLink":"13zbPhkw6Wccwa9QPvUYFKEcEvLqHk9c9KY-9EQkMqo0","sheetName":"Eva - Module Template V1.0 - CoronaGo","tab":"List Pages","type":"Warning","problem":"Column field `Date of Birth` not found in datamodel","solution":"Configure value for the column in list page","rowIdx":"4","column":"6"},{"id":20,"sheetLink":"13zbPhkw6Wccwa9QPvUYFKEcEvLqHk9c9KY-9EQkMqo0","sheetName":"Eva - Module Template V1.0 - CoronaGo","tab":"List Pages","type":"Warning","problem":"Column field `Date of Birth` not found in datamodel","solution":"Configure value for the column in list page","rowIdx":"4","column":"6"},{"id":21,"sheetLink":"13zbPhkw6Wccwa9QPvUYFKEcEvLqHk9c9KY-9EQkMqo0","sheetName":"Eva - Module Template V1.0 - CoronaGo","tab":"List Pages","type":"Warning","problem":"Column field `Date of Birth` not found in datamodel","solution":"Configure value for the column in list page","rowIdx":"5","column":"6"},{"id":22,"sheetLink":"13zbPhkw6Wccwa9QPvUYFKEcEvLqHk9c9KY-9EQkMqo0","sheetName":"Eva - Module Template V1.0 - CoronaGo","tab":"List Pages","type":"Warning","problem":"Column field `Date of Birth` not found in datamodel","solution":"Configure value for the column in list page","rowIdx":"5","column":"6"},{"id":23,"sheetLink":"13zbPhkw6Wccwa9QPvUYFKEcEvLqHk9c9KY-9EQkMqo0","sheetName":"Eva - Module Template V1.0 - CoronaGo","tab":"List Pages","type":"Warning","problem":"Column field `Date of Birth` not found in datamodel","solution":"Configure value for the column in list page","rowIdx":"6","column":"6"},{"id":24,"sheetLink":"13zbPhkw6Wccwa9QPvUYFKEcEvLqHk9c9KY-9EQkMqo0","sheetName":"Eva - Module Template V1.0 - CoronaGo","tab":"List Pages","type":"Warning","problem":"Column field `Date of Birth` not found in datamodel","solution":"Configure value for the column in list page","rowIdx":"6","column":"6"},{"id":25,"sheetLink":"13zbPhkw6Wccwa9QPvUYFKEcEvLqHk9c9KY-9EQkMqo0","sheetName":"Eva - Module Template V1.0 - CoronaGo","tab":"List Pages","type":"Warning","problem":"Column field `Date of Birth` not found in datamodel","solution":"Configure value for the column in list page","rowIdx":"7","column":"6"},{"id":26,"sheetLink":"13zbPhkw6Wccwa9QPvUYFKEcEvLqHk9c9KY-9EQkMqo0","sheetName":"Eva - Module Template V1.0 - CoronaGo","tab":"List Pages","type":"Warning","problem":"Column field `Date of Birth` not found in datamodel","solution":"Configure value for the column in list page","rowIdx":"7","column":"6"},{"id":27,"sheetLink":"13zbPhkw6Wccwa9QPvUYFKEcEvLqHk9c9KY-9EQkMqo0","sheetName":"Eva - Module Template V1.0 - CoronaGo","tab":"List Pages","type":"Warning","problem":"Column field `Date of Birth` not found in datamodel","solution":"Configure value for the column in list page","rowIdx":"8","column":"6"},{"id":28,"sheetLink":"13zbPhkw6Wccwa9QPvUYFKEcEvLqHk9c9KY-9EQkMqo0","sheetName":"Eva - Module Template V1.0 - CoronaGo","tab":"List Pages","type":"Warning","problem":"Column field `Date of Birth` not found in datamodel","solution":"Configure value for the column in list page","rowIdx":"8","column":"6"}]},{"id":10,"action":"Detail Page Generation","dateTime":1585117259144,"items":[{"id":1,"sheetLink":"13zbPhkw6Wccwa9QPvUYFKEcEvLqHk9c9KY-9EQkMqo0","sheetName":"Eva - Module Template V1.0 - CoronaGo","tab":"Data Model","type":"Warning","problem":"Allowed values are missing for `Hospital Name`","solution":"For Data type Checkbox/CheckboxGroup/DropDown/RadioButton/Multiselect allowed values should be configured","rowIdx":"59","column":"7"},{"id":2,"sheetLink":"13zbPhkw6Wccwa9QPvUYFKEcEvLqHk9c9KY-9EQkMqo0","sheetName":"Eva - Module Template V1.0 - CoronaGo","tab":"Data Model","type":"Warning","problem":"Allowed values are missing for `Item`","solution":"For Data type Checkbox/CheckboxGroup/DropDown/RadioButton/Multiselect allowed values should be configured","rowIdx":"60","column":"7"},{"id":3,"sheetLink":"13zbPhkw6Wccwa9QPvUYFKEcEvLqHk9c9KY-9EQkMqo0","sheetName":"Eva - Module Template V1.0 - CoronaGo","tab":"Data Model","type":"Warning","problem":"Allowed values are missing for `Item`","solution":"For Data type Checkbox/CheckboxGroup/DropDown/RadioButton/Multiselect allowed values should be configured","rowIdx":"63","column":"7"},{"id":4,"sheetLink":"13zbPhkw6Wccwa9QPvUYFKEcEvLqHk9c9KY-9EQkMqo0","sheetName":"Eva - Module Template V1.0 - CoronaGo","tab":"Data Model","type":"Warning","problem":"Allowed values are missing for `Patient Hid`","solution":"For Data type Checkbox/CheckboxGroup/DropDown/RadioButton/Multiselect allowed values should be configured","rowIdx":"38","column":"7"},{"id":5,"sheetLink":"13zbPhkw6Wccwa9QPvUYFKEcEvLqHk9c9KY-9EQkMqo0","sheetName":"Eva - Module Template V1.0 - CoronaGo","tab":"Data Model","type":"Warning","problem":"Allowed values are missing for `Patient Name`","solution":"For Data type Checkbox/CheckboxGroup/DropDown/RadioButton/Multiselect allowed values should be configured","rowIdx":"39","column":"7"},{"id":6,"sheetLink":"13zbPhkw6Wccwa9QPvUYFKEcEvLqHk9c9KY-9EQkMqo0","sheetName":"Eva - Module Template V1.0 - CoronaGo","tab":"Data Model","type":"Warning","problem":"Allowed values are missing for `Meeting Id`","solution":"For Data type Checkbox/CheckboxGroup/DropDown/RadioButton/Multiselect allowed values should be configured","rowIdx":"41","column":"7"},{"id":7,"sheetLink":"13zbPhkw6Wccwa9QPvUYFKEcEvLqHk9c9KY-9EQkMqo0","sheetName":"Eva - Module Template V1.0 - CoronaGo","tab":"Data Model","type":"Warning","problem":"Allowed values are missing for `Doctor Id`","solution":"For Data type Checkbox/CheckboxGroup/DropDown/RadioButton/Multiselect allowed values should be configured","rowIdx":"42","column":"7"},{"id":8,"sheetLink":"13zbPhkw6Wccwa9QPvUYFKEcEvLqHk9c9KY-9EQkMqo0","sheetName":"Eva - Module Template V1.0 - CoronaGo","tab":"Data Model","type":"Warning","problem":"Allowed values are missing for `Doctor Name`","solution":"For Data type Checkbox/CheckboxGroup/DropDown/RadioButton/Multiselect allowed values should be configured","rowIdx":"43","column":"7"},{"id":9,"sheetLink":"13zbPhkw6Wccwa9QPvUYFKEcEvLqHk9c9KY-9EQkMqo0","sheetName":"Eva - Module Template V1.0 - CoronaGo","tab":"Data Model","type":"Warning","problem":"Allowed values are missing for `Meeting Status`","solution":"For Data type Checkbox/CheckboxGroup/DropDown/RadioButton/Multiselect allowed values should be configured","rowIdx":"47","column":"7"},{"id":10,"sheetLink":"13zbPhkw6Wccwa9QPvUYFKEcEvLqHk9c9KY-9EQkMqo0","sheetName":"Eva - Module Template V1.0 - CoronaGo","tab":"Data Model","type":"Warning","problem":"Allowed values are missing for `Meeting Url`","solution":"For Data type Checkbox/CheckboxGroup/DropDown/RadioButton/Multiselect allowed values should be configured","rowIdx":"48","column":"7"},{"id":11,"sheetLink":"13zbPhkw6Wccwa9QPvUYFKEcEvLqHk9c9KY-9EQkMqo0","sheetName":"Eva - Module Template V1.0 - CoronaGo","tab":"Data Model","type":"Warning","problem":"Allowed values are missing for `Doctor Name`","solution":"For Data type Checkbox/CheckboxGroup/DropDown/RadioButton/Multiselect allowed values should be configured","rowIdx":"52","column":"7"},{"id":12,"sheetLink":"13zbPhkw6Wccwa9QPvUYFKEcEvLqHk9c9KY-9EQkMqo0","sheetName":"Eva - Module Template V1.0 - CoronaGo","tab":"Data Model","type":"Warning","problem":"Allowed values are missing for `Item`","solution":"For Data type Checkbox/CheckboxGroup/DropDown/RadioButton/Multiselect allowed values should be configured","rowIdx":"56","column":"7"},{"id":13,"sheetLink":"13zbPhkw6Wccwa9QPvUYFKEcEvLqHk9c9KY-9EQkMqo0","sheetName":"Eva - Module Template V1.0 - CoronaGo","tab":"Data Model","type":"Warning","problem":"Allowed values are missing for `Patient Name`","solution":"For Data type Checkbox/CheckboxGroup/DropDown/RadioButton/Multiselect allowed values should be configured","rowIdx":"74","column":"7"},{"id":14,"sheetLink":"13zbPhkw6Wccwa9QPvUYFKEcEvLqHk9c9KY-9EQkMqo0","sheetName":"Eva - Module Template V1.0 - CoronaGo","tab":"Data Model","type":"Warning","problem":"Allowed values are missing for `Patient HId`","solution":"For Data type Checkbox/CheckboxGroup/DropDown/RadioButton/Multiselect allowed values should be configured","rowIdx":"76","column":"7"},{"id":15,"sheetLink":"13zbPhkw6Wccwa9QPvUYFKEcEvLqHk9c9KY-9EQkMqo0","sheetName":"Eva - Module Template V1.0 - CoronaGo","tab":"Data Model","type":"Warning","problem":"Allowed values are missing for `City`","solution":"For Data type Checkbox/CheckboxGroup/DropDown/RadioButton/Multiselect allowed values should be configured","rowIdx":"81","column":"7"},{"id":16,"sheetLink":"13zbPhkw6Wccwa9QPvUYFKEcEvLqHk9c9KY-9EQkMqo0","sheetName":"Eva - Module Template V1.0 - CoronaGo","tab":"Data Model","type":"Warning","problem":"Allowed values are missing for `Insurance Provider`","solution":"For Data type Checkbox/CheckboxGroup/DropDown/RadioButton/Multiselect allowed values should be configured","rowIdx":"83","column":"7"},{"id":17,"sheetLink":"13zbPhkw6Wccwa9QPvUYFKEcEvLqHk9c9KY-9EQkMqo0","sheetName":"Eva - Module Template V1.0 - CoronaGo","tab":"Data Model","type":"Warning","problem":"Allowed values are missing for `Patient Name`","solution":"For Data type Checkbox/CheckboxGroup/DropDown/RadioButton/Multiselect allowed values should be configured","rowIdx":"6","column":"7"},{"id":18,"sheetLink":"13zbPhkw6Wccwa9QPvUYFKEcEvLqHk9c9KY-9EQkMqo0","sheetName":"Eva - Module Template V1.0 - CoronaGo","tab":"Data Model","type":"Warning","problem":"Allowed values are missing for `Patient HId`","solution":"For Data type Checkbox/CheckboxGroup/DropDown/RadioButton/Multiselect allowed values should be configured","rowIdx":"8","column":"7"},{"id":19,"sheetLink":"13zbPhkw6Wccwa9QPvUYFKEcEvLqHk9c9KY-9EQkMqo0","sheetName":"Eva - Module Template V1.0 - CoronaGo","tab":"List Pages","type":"Warning","problem":"Column field `Date of Birth` not found in datamodel","solution":"Configure value for the column in list page","rowIdx":"4","column":"6"},{"id":20,"sheetLink":"13zbPhkw6Wccwa9QPvUYFKEcEvLqHk9c9KY-9EQkMqo0","sheetName":"Eva - Module Template V1.0 - CoronaGo","tab":"List Pages","type":"Warning","problem":"Column field `Date of Birth` not found in datamodel","solution":"Configure value for the column in list page","rowIdx":"4","column":"6"},{"id":21,"sheetLink":"13zbPhkw6Wccwa9QPvUYFKEcEvLqHk9c9KY-9EQkMqo0","sheetName":"Eva - Module Template V1.0 - CoronaGo","tab":"List Pages","type":"Warning","problem":"Column field `Date of Birth` not found in datamodel","solution":"Configure value for the column in list page","rowIdx":"5","column":"6"},{"id":22,"sheetLink":"13zbPhkw6Wccwa9QPvUYFKEcEvLqHk9c9KY-9EQkMqo0","sheetName":"Eva - Module Template V1.0 - CoronaGo","tab":"List Pages","type":"Warning","problem":"Column field `Date of Birth` not found in datamodel","solution":"Configure value for the column in list page","rowIdx":"5","column":"6"},{"id":23,"sheetLink":"13zbPhkw6Wccwa9QPvUYFKEcEvLqHk9c9KY-9EQkMqo0","sheetName":"Eva - Module Template V1.0 - CoronaGo","tab":"List Pages","type":"Warning","problem":"Column field `Date of Birth` not found in datamodel","solution":"Configure value for the column in list page","rowIdx":"6","column":"6"},{"id":24,"sheetLink":"13zbPhkw6Wccwa9QPvUYFKEcEvLqHk9c9KY-9EQkMqo0","sheetName":"Eva - Module Template V1.0 - CoronaGo","tab":"List Pages","type":"Warning","problem":"Column field `Date of Birth` not found in datamodel","solution":"Configure value for the column in list page","rowIdx":"6","column":"6"},{"id":25,"sheetLink":"13zbPhkw6Wccwa9QPvUYFKEcEvLqHk9c9KY-9EQkMqo0","sheetName":"Eva - Module Template V1.0 - CoronaGo","tab":"List Pages","type":"Warning","problem":"Column field `Date of Birth` not found in datamodel","solution":"Configure value for the column in list page","rowIdx":"7","column":"6"},{"id":26,"sheetLink":"13zbPhkw6Wccwa9QPvUYFKEcEvLqHk9c9KY-9EQkMqo0","sheetName":"Eva - Module Template V1.0 - CoronaGo","tab":"List Pages","type":"Warning","problem":"Column field `Date of Birth` not found in datamodel","solution":"Configure value for the column in list page","rowIdx":"7","column":"6"},{"id":27,"sheetLink":"13zbPhkw6Wccwa9QPvUYFKEcEvLqHk9c9KY-9EQkMqo0","sheetName":"Eva - Module Template V1.0 - CoronaGo","tab":"List Pages","type":"Warning","problem":"Column field `Date of Birth` not found in datamodel","solution":"Configure value for the column in list page","rowIdx":"8","column":"6"},{"id":28,"sheetLink":"13zbPhkw6Wccwa9QPvUYFKEcEvLqHk9c9KY-9EQkMqo0","sheetName":"Eva - Module Template V1.0 - CoronaGo","tab":"List Pages","type":"Warning","problem":"Column field `Date of Birth` not found in datamodel","solution":"Configure value for the column in list page","rowIdx":"8","column":"6"}]}];

/***/ })

}]);
//# sourceMappingURL=0.js.map